我希望他们可以说是集群的联赛，因为那时天气很好
I wish they can say that the cluster's League because the weather is nice then
League because the weather is nice then that would be a very reasonable excuse
这将是一个非常合理的借口，但是随着学期的进行
that would be a very reasonable excuse but as the semester progresses
but as the semester progresses everybody's coming later and later later
每个人都迟迟不来我什至不带手表
everybody's coming later and later later I don't even bring my watch anymore but
I don't even bring my watch anymore but unfortunately I can see the time there
不幸的是我可以在那里看到时间
因此，如果您还记得我们在谈论，我们实际上开始谈论做
I don't even bring my watch anymore but unfortunately I can see the time there
so if you remember we were talking we start talking actually about doing
因此，如果您还记得我们在谈论，我们实际上开始谈论做
start talking actually about doing maximum likelihood estimation for the
无向图形中参数的最大似然估计
maximum likelihood estimation for the parameters in undirected graphical
parameters in undirected graphical models so I'm going to continue that
模型，因此我将继续该主题，但我意识到其中一些
models so I'm going to continue that topic but I realized that some of the
topic but I realized that some of the the you know the algorithm is a little
你知道算法比你们要复杂一些
the you know the algorithm is a little bit more complicated than you guys are
bit more complicated than you guys are ready to take on a sunny day so I'm
准备好在阳光明媚的日子里，所以今天我要把盒子拿回去
ready to take on a sunny day so I'm going to take sort of the box back today
going to take sort of the box back today and I I'm gonna review this parameter
我将审查此参数估计以完整描述
and I I'm gonna review this parameter estimation for completely describe to
estimation for completely describe to observe graphical models first starting
首先观察带有有向图的底图，然后观察图形模型
observe graphical models first starting with the under with directed graphs and
with the under with directed graphs and then I'm going to give you some
那么我将为您介绍无向图
then I'm going to give you some introduction for undirected graph so
introduction for undirected graph so when we come on the next lecture we can
当我们进行下一堂课时，我们可以从
when we come on the next lecture we can complete the the previous notes from
complete the the previous notes from last Tuesday right like sometimes the
上个星期二，就像今​​天的演讲有时是基本的
last Tuesday right like sometimes the lecture today is elementary on some
lecture today is elementary on some other point of view it's actually more
从其他角度来看，它实际上更复杂，因为它涉及概念
other point of view it's actually more complicated because it involves concepts
complicated because it involves concepts that we have already seen in the
我们已经在作业中看到了
that we have already seen in the homework yet
基本上有兴趣学习有向无向的参数
well interested basically to learn the parameters of directed undirected
parameters of directed undirected graphical models where we assume that we
假设我们拥有所需的所有数据的图形模型
graphical models where we assume that we have all the data we need this
have all the data we need this non-observable
不可观察，所以有人给您识别器
non-observable so somebody gives you the recognizer
so somebody gives you the recognizer calmodulin space you know what I have
钙调素空间，你知道我在图中所有节点上都有数据吗？
calmodulin space you know what I have data on all nodes in the graph can you
data on all nodes in the graph can you go and estimate the parameters
去估计参数，我们有兴趣回到
go and estimate the parameters and we're interested to go back to the
and we're interested to go back to the problem we discussed on Tuesday which is
我们在星期二讨论的问题是最大似然估计，因此我可以
problem we discussed on Tuesday which is maximum likelihood estimation so I can
maximum likelihood estimation so I can tell you what the outcome of the lecture
告诉你今天的演讲结果是什么，但对于裁判来说
tell you what the outcome of the lecture today is going to be but for the referee
today is going to be but for the referee graphical models the parameter
图形化模型，参数估计解耦为一个小艾米莉（Emily）
graphical models the parameter estimation decouples as one little Emily
estimation decouples as one little Emily problem of this node so basically you
这个节点的问题，所以基本上您可以在本地计算参数
problem of this node so basically you can calculate the parameters locally in
can calculate the parameters locally in the graph so this is very trivial very
该图，因此对于无向而言，这是非常琐碎且非常有吸引力的
the graph so this is very trivial very attractive to do for undirected
attractive to do for undirected graphical mode for undirected graphical
蒙特卡洛字段的无向图形模型的图形模式，我们已经准备好
graphical mode for undirected graphical model for Montecarlo fields we're ready
model for Montecarlo fields we're ready started discussing this on Tuesday
由于归一化因素D，于星期二开始讨论此问题
started discussing this on Tuesday because of the normalization factors D
because of the normalization factors D you cannot really be couple it this
你真的不能很好地将它与夫妇相处，所以整个问题需要
you cannot really be couple it this nicely so the whole problem needs to
nicely so the whole problem needs to come together and compute all the
一起计算所有技巧的所有参数，因为
come together and compute all the parameters for all the tricks because
parameters for all the tricks because this G factor includes all the
该G因子包括所有信息，因此不允许
this G factor includes all the information so this does not allow the
information so this does not allow the coffee now there is a very special type
咖啡现在有一种非常特殊的无向图形模型，即
coffee now there is a very special type of undirected graphical models that is
of undirected graphical models that is called the composable models where
称为可组合模型，通过某种方式我们可以在本地进行很多
called the composable models where somehow we can do a many locally and
somehow we can do a many locally and this is what I want to discuss today and
这是我今天要讨论的，所以有一些相对完整的
this is what I want to discuss today and so there is some relative that complete
so there is some relative that complete the Emily solution and this algorithms
艾米丽（Emily）解决方案，该算法在本地是可以的，因此对于辩证法
the Emily solution and this algorithms are local okay so for dialectic
are local okay so for dialectic graphical models we're going to see the
图形模型，如果我们有一个
graphical models we're going to see the problem is really trivial if we have a
problem is really trivial if we have a completely observed model for the record
完全观察的模型用于记录图形模型，这变得容易
completely observed model for the record graphical models it becomes an easy
graphical models it becomes an easy thing for what is called the composable
所谓的可组合捆绑的东西，否则你仍然可以做一些
thing for what is called the composable bundle otherwise still you can do some
bundle otherwise still you can do some iterations and we will see what type of
迭代，我们将看到我们将拥有哪种类型的文件
iterations and we will see what type of file would we have
file would we have to discuss them much I'm gonna take a
讨论很多，我要退后一步，讨论琐碎的事
to discuss them much I'm gonna take a step backwards and discuss the trivial
step backwards and discuss the trivial problem first of directed graphical
首先是有向图模型的问题，然后看看为什么这有点像
problem first of directed graphical models and see why this is sort of a
models and see why this is sort of a trivial situation I realize she's
琐碎的情况我意识到她越来越热
trivial situation I realize she's getting hot
因此，我们考虑一个非常简单的指令图形软糖，您会注意到所有
so we consider a very simple directive graphical fondant and you notice all the
graphical fondant and you notice all the notes are observed right and so if you
音符被正确观察，因此，如果您尝试写出联合概率
notes are observed right and so if you try to write the joint probability
try to write the joint probability distribution of course you may have P of
当然，您可能将x的P赋给了那个，所以这就是
distribution of course you may have P of x1 given to that one so this is the
x1 given to that one so this is the transfer ominous theta one then you have
转移不祥的theta一个，那么你给x2的P赋予x1自己的参数，
transfer ominous theta one then you have P of x2 given x1 its own parameters and
P of x2 given x1 its own parameters and finally P of X for given x2 and x3 with
给定x2和x3以及它自己的参数2的X的最终P 7月1日
finally P of X for given x2 and x3 with its own parameters 2 1 July will you
its own parameters 2 1 July will you write down the log life it looks like
写下日志的样子，这样您就可以立即了解为什么
write down the log life it looks like that so you can immediately see why this
that so you can immediately see why this is a trivial problem to discuss about
在记录图中讨论有关Emily估计的琐碎问题
is a trivial problem to discuss about Emily estimation in the record graphs
Emily estimation in the record graphs when you have fully prescribed data
当您具有完全规定的数据时，因为如果您看theta 1
when you have fully prescribed data because if you look at theta 1 it only
because if you look at theta 1 it only comes in this term if you look at see
如果您看到这两个词，它只会出现在这里等
comes in this term if you look at see the two it only comes here etcetera
the two it only comes here etcetera etcetera so really if you want to
etcetera，所以如果您想进行任何计算，那么如果真的要对其进行计算
etcetera so really if you want to compute it along if you can do any many
compute it along if you can do any many problem on the first time if you want to
第一次出现问题，如果您想计算θ2或第二项
problem on the first time if you want to do to compute theta 2 or the second term
do to compute theta 2 or the second term etc so effectively the problem
等有效地将问题分解为很少的优化
etc so effectively the problem decomposes to little optimization
decomposes to little optimization problems defined in its node all right
他们需要知道在其节点中定义的问题，您还记得吗
problems defined in its node all right they need to know do you remember the
they need to know do you remember the probability involves the node and the
概率涉及节点和节点的路径，所以
probability involves the node and the path of the node all right so
path of the node all right so information that for example if you try
例如，如果您尝试计算theta 2的信息，显然
information that for example if you try to compute theta 2 obviously the
to compute theta 2 obviously the observations X 1 and X 2 completely at
观测X 1和X 2完全完全一样，所以当我们必须至少看到四个
observations X 1 and X 2 completely at all so when we have to see at least four
all so when we have to see at least four discrete models how people get fitter to
离散模型人们如何变得更健康以提供信息
discrete models how people get fitter to give an information
give an information x1 and x2 in essence what the Emily
从本质上讲，x1和x2变成了艾米丽（Emily）问题
x1 and x2 in essence what the Emily problem becomes becomes a bunch of
problem becomes becomes a bunch of separate Emily problems define for its
单独的Emily问题为其节点和您看到的这个小图定义
separate Emily problems define for its node and this little graph that you see
node and this little graph that you see involve to no than the parts okay so in
涉及的部分不多，所以可以通过很多方式在其中运行
involve to no than the parts okay so in in many ways you can run this in
in many ways you can run this in parallel and it's as we received surveys
并行，这是因为我们收到了调查分析解决方案的八种
parallel and it's as we received surveys analytical solution eight sort of a
analytical solution eight sort of a trivial problem
琐碎的问题，所以让我们来吧，因为我将需要
trivial problem so let's because I'm gonna need the
so let's because I'm gonna need the notation in the context of Markov random
马尔可夫随机场上下文中的符号，所以让我们介绍一下这种符号
notation in the context of Markov random field so let's introduce this notation
field so let's introduce this notation for directed models so we have a graph
对于定向模型，所以我们有一个图好吧，这是注释的数量
for directed models so we have a graph okay this is the number of notes a
okay this is the number of notes a number of edges xu is random variable
边数xu是随机变量，在图中与您的注释相关
number of edges xu is random variable affiliated with a note you in the graph
affiliated with a note you in the graph the little xu is the realization of
小x就是你的资本X的实现
the little xu is the realization of capital X of you capital X with
capital X of you capital X with subscript T is basically the random
下标T基本上是与G的子集G相关的随机变量隶属关系
subscript T is basically the random variables affiliation with a subset G of
variables affiliation with a subset G of the notes alright
笔记很好，这将是一个非常有用的
the notes alright and this would be a very useful
and this would be a very useful important location actually today and
实际上是今天的重要位置，因为我们使用X下标C来描述
important location actually today and because we use X subscript C to describe
because we use X subscript C to describe the random variables on the subset say
子集上的随机变量表示我们要使用X和
the random variables on the subset say we're going instead of using X and
we're going instead of using X and scribe order on the volume which we're
在体积上标出顺序，我们将用X下标V来描述
scribe order on the volume which we're going to put X subscript V to describe
going to put X subscript V to describe other of the variables in the graph as
图中的其他变量也一样，所以分布分解
other of the variables in the graph as well okay so the distribution factorizes
well okay so the distribution factorizes basically this is the fundamental
基本上，这是有向图作为产品的基本属性
basically this is the fundamental property of directed graphs as a product
property of directed graphs as a product of these local distributions for it's no
这些本地分布是因为这不是用语的条件，而这些是
of these local distributions for it's no condition of the parlance and these are
condition of the parlance and these are the unknown parameters that we want to
我们想要计算的未知参数基本上是这样的
the unknown parameters that we want to compute okay so basically this
compute okay so basically this parameters if the variables are discrete
参数，如果变量是离散的，则它们基本上是
parameters if the variables are discrete they are basically the values that the
they are basically the values that the XQ takes the tray value i given the
XQ取我给定的托盘值
XQ takes the tray value i given the defines
defines take a value J
取值J，但我们现在只表示参数
take a value J but we just denote the parameters now
but we just denote the parameters now asleep thank you but really for the
睡着了，谢谢，但实际上是街上的模型参数
asleep thank you but really for the street models the parameters
street models the parameters v IQ is the table that gives you the
v IQ是可为您提供有关此条件的信息的表
v IQ is the table that gives you the information about this conditional
information about this conditional distribution where can we have n
分布在哪里我们可以有n个观测值，并确定是
distribution where can we have n observations and sure that is
observations and sure that is interesting and observations means I
有趣和观察意味着我有n个观察，每个观察
interesting and observations means I have n observations and each observation
have n observations and each observation involves values of all the nodes in the
涉及到图中所有节点的值，因为一切正常
involves values of all the nodes in the graph because everything is observed ok
graph because everything is observed ok so there is not hidden variables so
所以没有隐藏的变量，所以在我们所做的一切中，
so there is not hidden variables so again in everything we have done up to
again in everything we have done up to now when we still have n observations we
现在当我们仍有n个观察值时，图中可能会有一些变量
now when we still have n observations we may have some variables in the graph
may have some variables in the graph here we apply all the the realizations
在这里，我们应用图中给出的所有实现，并且我们有n个
here we apply all the the realizations are given in the graph and we have n of
are given in the graph and we have n of those right n observations okay so let's
那些正确的n个观察结果好吧，让我们检查一下如何将其写成
those right n observations okay so let's check how we are going to write this in
check how we are going to write this in some sense what we have is we have n
从某种意义上说，我们拥有n个副本或20个描述概率
some sense what we have is we have n replicas or a 20 describe probabilistic
replicas or a 20 describe probabilistic directly graphical model you Bri so you
Bri的直接图形模型，所以您知道我是否要给您所有这些信息
directly graphical model you Bri so you know if I say I give you all of these
know if I say I give you all of these nodes prescribed one realization I will
节点规定了一种实现，我将再给你一个和另一个，并且
nodes prescribed one realization I will give you another one and another one and
give you another one and another one and another one really a heav n realizations
另一个真的很重，我有n种不同的图形模型
another one really a heav n realizations I have n different graphical models
I have n different graphical models obviously it's not convenient to think
显然，认为使用图形模型并不方便，因此
obviously it's not convenient to think that you work with an graphical model so
that you work with an graphical model so somehow when we do the analysis we will
不知何故，当我们进行分析时，我们将需要某种方式来获取此信息
somehow when we do the analysis we will need sort of to take this information
need sort of to take this information and and somehow composited in a way that
并以某种方式进行合成，我们可以将这些概率用于一个
and and somehow composited in a way that we can use these probability for one
we can use these probability for one stinking graph G ok but right now the
臭的图G好的，但现在看起来像这样的样子
stinking graph G ok but right now the way that this looks like ok it's like
way that this looks like ok it's like that and so it's maybe back home to
这样，也许是回家描述发生了什么事，所以我可以
that and so it's maybe back home to describe what is going on so I could
describe what is going on so I could describe if you want to describe the end
描述您是否要描述二十个副本的结尾
describe if you want to describe the end for this replicas of the twenty
for this replicas of the twenty described
描述直接灌浆甚至不得不写成
described directly grout even have to write it as
directly grout even have to write it as xB which is all the notes or theoretical
xB，这是所有注释或理论值，如果您想这样做，该怎么办？
xB which is all the notes or theoretical and what if you want to do this for a
and what if you want to do this for a subset of note C then you have to again
注释C的子集，那么您必须再次引用一些副本，好吧，它是
subset of note C then you have to again refer to some replicas and okay so it's
refer to some replicas and okay so it's a little bit awkward to do that so the
这样做有点尴尬，所以观察到的数据集是所有
a little bit awkward to do that so the observed data set is the values of all
observed data set is the values of all the notes and we have this given n times
笔记，我们又给了n次，我希望你能确保你
the notes and we have this given n times again I want you to be sure that you
again I want you to be sure that you understand this each of this are the
理解这一点，每个都是X的计时码表的值
understand this each of this are the values of X's every cronograph alright
values of X's every cronograph alright and we have n realizations below
我们在下面有n个实现，因此可能性写为
and we have n realizations below so the likelihood is written as the
so the likelihood is written as the product over each of this replicas of
每个图的可能性的每个副本的乘积
product over each of this replicas of the likelihood for each graph and given
the likelihood for each graph and given the parameters so I have n data you know
参数，所以我有n个数据，你知道我有一个数据集的乘积
the parameters so I have n data you know I have a product over with the data set
I have a product over with the data set and then the factorization of the Joint
然后每个图上的联合分布的因式分解都结束了
and then the factorization of the Joint Distribution over each graph is over
Distribution over each graph is over nodes right and I put a subscript u
节点正确，我在这里放了一个下标，在此明确指出，
nodes right and I put a subscript u there and here clear precise that this
there and here clear precise that this refers to the replica and anybody
指副本，任何人都跟随
refers to the replica and anybody follows
正确，我们给出的是观察值的数量以及每个观察值
right we're giving and number of observations and each observation
observations and each observation involves the values of for the notes in
涉及图表中注释的值，好吧，我想写什么
involves the values of for the notes in a graph alright so what I want to write
a graph alright so what I want to write a likelihood I'm going to have first
我首先要考虑的是这种可能性的乘积
a likelihood I'm going to have first over a product of the likelihood of this
over a product of the likelihood of this replicas here want to up to n right so
这里的副本要最多n个，所以这是一个产品，然后我要
replicas here want to up to n right so this is a product and then I'm going to
this is a product and then I'm going to have to light the light with a picture
必须用这张图的图片来照亮我的意思是课程的大部分内容
have to light the light with a picture of this graph I mean much of the course
of this graph I mean much of the course up to now has been the likelihood of a
到现在为止，只有一张图的可能性很大，但是现在，因为完全
up to now has been the likelihood of a single graph but now because fully
single graph but now because fully describe I have a likelihood over an
描述我有可能选择图表的s
describe I have a likelihood over an elective s of the graph and it'd be
elective s of the graph and it'd be different okay so and this distribution
不同，这样，此副本的此分发结束就被写入了
different okay so and this distribution for this replica end it is written in
for this replica end it is written in the classical way is the product of the
对于父母给你的每一个音符，经典的方式都是徐的产物
the classical way is the product of the Xu for every note you given the parents
Xu for every note you given the parents alright and peter view of the parameters
可以很好地查看这些参数，但您知道定义的条件
alright and peter view of the parameters but you know the defined that condition
but you know the defined that condition distribution so we take the log
分布，所以我们将对数似然对数变成公众
distribution so we take the log likelihood right the public becomes
likelihood right the public becomes summations it looks like that can you
总结一下，您现在可以立即看到为什么这个Emily
summations it looks like that can you see now immediately why this Emily
see now immediately why this Emily estimation the couple's can look at this
估计这对夫妇可以看这个方程式，我什么也没读
estimation the couple's can look at this equation I don't read anything in the
equation I don't read anything in the text etc so we can move faster today and
文字等，所以我们今天可以快一点，告诉我看一下这个方程
text etc so we can move faster today and tell me look at this equation what
tell me look at this equation what information from the observations do we
来自观察的信息，我们是否需要计算参数theta
information from the observations do we need to compute the parameters theta you
need to compute the parameters theta you about having the conditional
关于有条件地分配条件分布
about having the conditional distribution affectionately given its
distribution affectionately given its products so what information how do you
产品，那么您如何知道什么信息就可以最大程度地利用这些信息
products so what information how do you you know maximize this with respect to
you know maximize this with respect to theta here for the given you
给你的theta
您有多少公司投资了两倍的总和？
you know maximize this with respect to theta here for the given you
in how many firms invest a double summation of these are you comes in
您有多少公司投资了两倍的总和？
summation of these are you comes in terms okay and only one of the
条款还可以，而且只有一项总结对您有效，那么什么是
terms okay and only one of the summations on you so what are the
summations on you so what are the cetacean statistics basically from the
鲸类统计数据基本上是从数据或至少看起来是什么
cetacean statistics basically from the data or at least what information looks
data or at least what information looks right now from all the data that it's
现在，从所有数据中，这些数据将对计算至关重要
right now from all the data that it's going to be essential in computing
going to be essential in computing p-type you looking at this the
p型，您在此查看非文本视图的观察结果
p-type you looking at this the observations of the non-text view in the
observations of the non-text view in the n electricals that we had and also the
我们拥有的电子设备以及当前评论中的信息
n electricals that we had and also the information on the current review
information on the current review there's no return for these things
这些东西没有回报，你会看到，如果他只是
there's no return for these things coming in you see that if that he only
coming in you see that if that he only comes it is you know the parameters are
来了，就是您知道此分发权中的参数即将到来
comes it is you know the parameters are coming in this distribution rights
coming in this distribution rights during installation of many of these
在安装许多这些发行版的过程中，所以今天您将
during installation of many of these distributions so today you will only be
distributions so today you will only be in all these terms 10 where we have the
在所有这些方面10我们在这里有青年，在这里有你们的父母
in all these terms 10 where we have the youth here you and the parents of you
youth here you and the parents of you there on the couple okay the only cover
那对夫妇好吧，现在唯一的掩护，我们不会告诉我
there on the couple okay the only cover all right now we will not tell me that
all right now we will not tell me that if this distribution is in the
如果这个分布在指数族中，那么我们实际上可以
if this distribution is in the exponential family right actually we can
exponential family right actually we can easily compute sufficient statistics all
可以轻松地计算出足够的统计数据，但是对于任何情况，基本上都可以，所以
easily compute sufficient statistics all right but for any and basically okay so
right but for any and basically okay so let's see how this is going to have
让我们看看这将是怎么回事
如此低效，我会变得有点复杂，我需要这个
right but for any and basically okay so let's see how this is going to have
so inefficient I was going to get a little bit complicated and I need this
如此低效，我会变得有点复杂，我需要这个
little bit complicated and I need this when throughout the lecture today so we
在今天整个讲座中，所以我们在所有道路上都有任何观察
when throughout the lecture today so we have any observations at all the roads
have any observations at all the roads being the go ok so let me introduce the
一切顺利，所以让我介绍以下定义，这样
being the go ok so let me introduce the following definition all right so the
following definition all right so the intellectual member is reinventions with
知识分子是具有组织下标的退休人员的革新
intellectual member is reinventions with a subscript retiarius the organization's
a subscript retiarius the organization's of all the variables so M affects V is
所有变量使M影响V的次数是我数据集中的次数
of all the variables so M affects V is the number of times that in my data set
the number of times that in my data set I escape this realization little extra
我正在使用离散工作来逃脱这种认识，所以不需要额外的下标
I escape this realization little extra subscript me I'm working with discrete
subscript me I'm working with discrete volume so it's every X takes a finite
所以每个X取有限数量的值，而我取一个
volume so it's every X takes a finite number of values and I'm taking a
number of values and I'm taking a collection of all the variables and I'm
所有变量的集合，我要求这个集合中的小X
collection of all the variables and I'm asking for this collection little X's
asking for this collection little X's realization of all of our images mean
我们所有图像的实现意味着有多少计数多少次，但是
realization of all of our images mean how many counts how many times but
how many counts how many times but collection for the variables happens on
变量的收集发生在我收集的数据集上
collection for the variables happens on the data set that I collected which is
the data set that I collected which is this n pint you ever and what the basis
这个n品脱你曾经是什么基础是这些三角洲的总和。
this n pint you ever and what the basis is the summation of these Delta
is the summation of these Delta functions or indicator functions to do
函数或指标函数，一旦它们做得更好，这给了我
functions or indicator functions to do once them even better and this gives me
once them even better and this gives me one every time XV coincides with X very
每次XV与X非常下标F重合时，您是否同意这就是我
one every time XV coincides with X very subscript F do you agree this is what I
subscript F do you agree this is what I have observed so if you gave me amounts
已经观察到，所以如果您给我一些跟随轴心的实现
have observed so if you gave me amounts of realizations who followed the axis
of realizations who followed the axis obviously the number of cows how many
显然，在我的数据集中发生这种情况的奶牛数量是
obviously the number of cows how many times in my data set this happens is the
times in my data set this happens is the summation of this
这个的总和
你知道有时候我想知道是否有人睡觉，然后我意识到有人
times in my data set this happens is the summation of this
you know sometimes I'm wonder if anybody sleeping and then I realized somebody
你知道有时候我想知道是否有人睡觉，然后我意识到有人
sleeping and then I realized somebody looks there they're so well okay yeah
看起来那里很好
是的
sleeping and then I realized somebody looks there they're so well okay yeah
yes
好的
all right
好吧，这又是X下标V是在黑暗中给予焦点的实现
okay so this again X subscript V is the realization of focus in the dark to give
realization of focus in the dark to give them a try on X 2 X 5 X 55 whatever you
他们尝试X 2 X 5 X 55不管你有多少倍
them a try on X 2 X 5 X 55 whatever you have the number of times the number of
have the number of times the number of cows that you see this in your observed
您在观察到的观察结果中看到的母牛是这次，我现在要去
cows that you see this in your observed observations is this time now I am going
observations is this time now I am going to introduce the notation for partial
引入部分帐户的表示法，始终订阅
to introduce the notation for partial accounts always subscripe of the
accounts always subscripe of the variables and I want you to look very
变量，我希望您对此方程仔细观察并说服
variables and I want you to look very carefully on this equation and convince
carefully on this equation and convince yourself that we understand it so we
您自己，我们了解它，所以我们介绍ffxv中的帐户数
yourself that we understand it so we introduce ffxv the number of accounts in
introduce ffxv the number of accounts in my data set of this observation section
我的观察部分2 XV的数据集现在可以定义了
my data set of this observation section 2 XV all right and now to define the
2 XV all right and now to define the partial count of a subset G unfold my
子集G的部分计数会展开我的笔记，好吧，我要做的就是
partial count of a subset G unfold my notes okay what I have to do is take
notes okay what I have to do is take this and sum it over all the
并将其加到V减去T的所有实现中，所以我知道
this and sum it over all the realizations in V minus T so I you know
realizations in V minus T so I you know I give the relationship C and I can
我给了关系C，我可以完成这个部分的tau
I give the relationship C and I can complete this partial tau all right
complete this partial tau all right by taking this and summing everything
通过求和并将除X下标C之外的所有内容相加，您得到一个
by taking this and summing everything except X subscript C and you have a
except X subscript C and you have a value so you say understand all the
值，所以您说了解其他所有可能的组合
value so you say understand all the possible combinations for the other
possible combinations for the other variables enough to give me the count
足以让我计算有效的变量，例如，如果我分享
variables enough to give me the count effective take for example if I share
effective take for example if I share three variables right and M of X 1 X 2 X
三个变量，X 1 X 2 X 3中的M是我的数据集中的次数
three variables right and M of X 1 X 2 X 3 is the number of times in my data set
3 is the number of times in my data set but capital X 1 takes the value little X
但是大写X 1取小X 1的值大写X 2取小X 2的值
but capital X 1 takes the value little X 1 capital X 2 takes the value little X 2
1 capital X 2 takes the value little X 2 capital X 3 X 1 a little extreme to
大写X 3 X 1有点极端，以定义在我的次数
capital X 3 X 1 a little extreme to define the number of times that in my
define the number of times that in my data stand I have a capital X 1 taking
数据架我有一个资本X 1，除以电子和资本
data stand I have a capital X 1 taking divided leave electron and capital
divided leave electron and capital actually
实际上，让我们做我需要做的就是
actually let's do what I have to do is take the
let's do what I have to do is take the count or for all the variables and some
计数或所有变量，并且有些极端有意义，是的，所以，
count or for all the variables and some extreme make sense yes all right so and
extreme make sense yes all right so and similarly mx1 I can comics to tear over
同样，MX1我可以将漫画撕毁，我可以输入X 2和X 3还是不行，所以
similarly mx1 I can comics to tear over I can some X 2 and X 3 or not okay so
I can some X 2 and X 3 or not okay so what I want you to remember is this is
我想让您记住的是，这是所有变量的XV计数M
what I want you to remember is this is the count M of X V for all the variables
the count M of X V for all the variables and this is a party account for a
这是变量成功的一方，这将
and this is a party account for a success of the variables and this would
success of the variables and this would be an essential thing right because we
是一件非常重要的事情，因为我们很快就会让您看到为什么，我们
be an essential thing right because we will have the you see shortly why and we
will have the you see shortly why and we try to solve them really well now look
尝试很好地解决它们，现在看一下这个方程式，告诉我这是为了
try to solve them really well now look at this equation and tell me this is for
at this equation and tell me this is for the example right but effectively if I
该示例是正确的，但如果我取所有变量的M效果V，则有效
the example right but effectively if I take M effects V of all the variables
take M effects V of all the variables and I sound for possible combinations of
然后我就XV的可能组合发出声音，然后我必须得到粒子和
and I sound for possible combinations of X V and then I have to get particle and
X V and then I have to get particle and there
那里
正确的
X V and then I have to get particle and there
right
在这里，我将所有可能的变量都实现了，但是它们
here I'm taking all possible realizations of my variables but they
realizations of my variables but they have only an observation so this sum has
只有一个观测值，所以这个总和必须等于资本F好的，让我
have only an observation so this sum has to be equal to capital F okay so let me
to be equal to capital F okay so let me introduce the last notation basically
基本上介绍最后一种表示法，然后我们就可以开始了
introduce the last notation basically then we're ready to go I'm going to
then we're ready to go I'm going to introduce a partial account for the
为您介绍的喜剧的喜剧介绍部分内容，以便
introduce a partial account for the comedy of the note you okay so the
comedy of the note you okay so the family of a note here is basically here
这里的音符系列基本上在调色板右边，我确实注意到
family of a note here is basically here in the palette right and I do notice as
in the palette right and I do notice as P of you okay so take some realizations
你们中的P好，所以请了解属于这个家庭的音符
P of you okay so take some realizations of the notes that belong to this family
of the notes that belong to this family of note view obviously the number of
注释视图的数量显然是您在数据集中看到此注释的次数
of note view obviously the number of times that you see this in your data set
times that you see this in your data set is the partial account which is
是部分帐户，如果您选择n个组织，则该帐户已完成
is the partial account which is completed if you take n of organizations
completed if you take n of organizations of X V and you sum for all values in
的值，您将这些注释中所有值的总和除
of X V and you sum for all values in these notes except the values that
these notes except the values that belong in the family of the note view
属于注释视图的家族，您会看到，这是
belong in the family of the note view you see that so this is the number of
you see that so this is the number of counts that you see and now do you take
您所看到的计数，现在您是否拥有一些价值，而巴黎则具有一些价值
counts that you see and now do you take some values and the Paris take some
some values and the Paris take some other value
其他值还可以，您可以通过
other value okay you can compute this by taking the
okay you can compute this by taking the total count over all the notes and
所有笔记的总数，除笔记之外的所有东西都加起来
total count over all the notes and summing everything but the notes that
summing everything but the notes that belong without stopping so let's turn I
属于而不停下来，所以让我们轮到我不必经历所有这一切，所以
belong without stopping so let's turn I don't have to go through all of this so
don't have to go through all of this so I'm looking on the equation of the
我正在寻找底部的等式，所以我们正在寻找
I'm looking on the equation of the bottom all right so we're looking for
bottom all right so we're looking for the likelihood of of
的可能性
我的观察结果中，我猜它们是绝对可能的
bottom all right so we're looking for the likelihood of of
of the observations I have and I'm guessing they're absolute most probably
我的观察结果中，我猜它们是绝对可能的
guessing they're absolute most probably it'd be okay
没关系，它在幻灯片11上，这样就可以了
it'd be okay it's on slide 11 this is fine as it is
it's on slide 11 this is fine as it is but you know it's better to put the
但是你知道最好把观测给定的概率
but you know it's better to put the probability of the observation of given
probability of the observation of given the parameters suddenly you're late and
参数突然你来晚了，在这之前我们都是方程式
the parameters suddenly you're late and we're all this equation before that this
we're all this equation before that this is the product of the likely which over
是可能性的产物，在此之上，eléctricas记得任何东西
is the product of the likely which over this and eléctricas remember anything
this and eléctricas remember anything else we can do so
否则我们可以这样做，所以我基本上有了产品
else we can do so okay so I have the product basically
okay so I have the product basically over and graphs right so this listen to
结束并正确绘制图形，这样就可以听取它们的声音，这就是每个
over and graphs right so this listen to them and this is the likelihood for each
them and this is the likelihood for each graph end of observing the data that I
观察我为演示提供的数据的图形端，这样
graph end of observing the data that I have given for the presentation okay so
have given for the presentation okay so now I'm going to do I won't be get rid
现在我要做的是，我不会摆脱这个索引十和这个乘积n
now I'm going to do I won't be get rid of this index ten and this product in n
of this index ten and this product in n so I'm going to start doing some algebra
所以我要开始做一些代数，所以我要写这个概率
so I'm going to start doing some algebra so I'm going to write this probability
so I'm going to write this probability for this replica and I'm gonna write it
这个复制品，我要写成这个产品，我想让你看看
for this replica and I'm gonna write it as this product and I want you to look
as this product and I want you to look and tell me that you understand
告诉我你明白
好的，所以我在这里做了什么，记得这次
as this product and I want you to look and tell me that you understand
all right so what exactly have I done here remember in in this time all right
好的，所以我在这里做了什么，记得这次
here remember in in this time all right I have a particular type of realization
我有一个特定类型的所有变量的正确实现X下标V
I have a particular type of realization of all the variables right X subscript V
of all the variables right X subscript V comma n is from the unreplicated the
逗号n来自未复制的所有节点的值
comma n is from the unreplicated the values of all the nodes in a lifeless as
values of all the nodes in a lifeless as the following take basically the
以下基本上以观察到X的概率为准
the following take basically the probability of observing little X
probability of observing little X subscript V rotational inertia flex V in
下标V仅在相反的实验皮层束中的旋转惯性挠曲V
subscript V rotational inertia flex V in only converse bunch of experi cortex
only converse bunch of experi cortex become an we have all those tricks
变成一个我们在没事之前就拥有了所有这些技巧
become an we have all those tricks actually before okay all right
actually before okay all right that's this equation on middle and then
那是中间的等式，然后注意
that's this equation on middle and then for notice that the probability
for notice that the probability basically of having the realizations of
基本上，只要给定参数，所有节点的实现都可以
basically of having the realizations of all the nodes okay given the parameters
all the nodes okay given the parameters is basically the product of the curve of
基本上是给定的父母概率曲线的乘积
is basically the product of the curve of the probabilities of the parents given a
the probabilities of the parents given a mean of the knowledge given the parents
给父母的知识的平均值，但最近安东尼的通知是
mean of the knowledge given the parents but with recent Anthony's notice that by
but with recent Anthony's notice that by doing this trick here the isness I only
在这里做这个技巧，我只在一个模型的可能性下工作
doing this trick here the isness I only worked with the probability of one model
worked with the probability of one model this is very important the subscription
这很重要，因为当我们
this is very important the subscription has been eliminated here right when we
has been eliminated here right when we start playing right so we have the
开始正确播放，所以这里有XV逗号n的可能性
start playing right so we have the probability of X V comma n here there is
probability of X V comma n here there is no anymore end the end has gone up to
再也没有结束了，到了三角洲功能，所以我们与
no anymore end the end has gone up to that delta function so we work with the
that delta function so we work with the probability the joint probability of one
概率仅一个图形模型的联合概率而不是n
probability the joint probability of one graphical model alone not of the n
graphical model alone not of the n replicas okay action
复制品可以采取的行动以及我实际想到的
replicas okay action and what practically done I think with
and what practically done I think with this slide take the log of this so this
此幻灯片记录了此日志，因此该产品将成为所有的总结
this slide take the log of this so this product is gonna become a summation all
product is gonna become a summation all right we don't like this gonna end there
对，我们不喜欢这样会结束，所以这个词将成为一个
right we don't like this gonna end there so this term is going to become a
so this term is going to become a summation
求和增量函数将下降，
summation the delta function will come down and
the delta function will come down and then we're going to have log of V of X V
那么给定theta，我们将获得XV的V的对数，这很好，因为这是
then we're going to have log of V of X V given theta this is nice because this is
given theta this is nice because this is the probability the love largely good
爱对我们的通用图权很大程度上有利的可能性不大
the probability the love largely good for our generic graph right does not
for our generic graph right does not involve any end and now notice if I take
涉及任何目的，现在请注意，如果我在这里进行求和，这是什么
involve any end and now notice if I take the summation here in n what is this
the summation here in n what is this summation giving me what is this
根据我们的定义，求和给我这个求和是什么
summation giving me what is this summation according to our definition
你知道我基本上通过了，所以这是可能的配置，所以
you know I go through basically okay so this is for possible configuration so
this is for possible configuration so then you know what I do is for each 6v I
那么您知道我要为每个6v做些什么，我正在检查多少次
then you know what I do is for each 6v I am checking how many times that
am checking how many times that exhibitions appear within my data set so
展览会出现在我的数据集中，所以这不是M XP的条款吗？
exhibitions appear within my data set so isn't it this the terms of M XP right
isn't it this the terms of M XP right okay
好吧，所以基本上，如果你在那里看
okay so basically if you look at this there
so basically if you look at this there is absolutely no end here now there's no
现在绝对没有尽头，没有模型的前身，我想画图
is absolutely no end here now there's no precursor of models etc I want to graph
precursor of models etc I want to graph alone but somehow the bank has been
一个人，但是不知何故，银行已经整合到了奶牛的数量中
alone but somehow the bank has been integrated in the number of cows of the
integrated in the number of cows of the observed X subscript V okay so let's put
观察到X下标V好吧，让我们放在这里
observed X subscript V okay so let's put in here
in here right so the log likelihood of all my
对，所以我所有观测值的对数似然又是这个，我写
right so the log likelihood of all my observations is this again and I write
observations is this again and I write this probability as long I factorize
只要我将其分解为条件概率
this probability as long I factorize this over the conditional probabilities
this over the conditional probabilities of bits now given the parent and I
现在给父母的位，我忘了提到条件
of bits now given the parent and I forgot to mention the condition
forgot to mention the condition probability I basically because we work
基本上是因为我喜欢离散变量，所以我很喜欢你
probability I basically because we work with discrete variables I liked it you
with discrete variables I liked it you know a parametric homeless parameters
知道属于主V的参数无家可归参数theta
know a parametric homeless parameters theta that belongs to the Lord V and
theta that belongs to the Lord V and their functions of the data at the node
它们在节点V及其产品上的数据功能
their functions of the data at the node V and it's product
V and it's product mr. Stanner petitioner could have
先生。鉴于X，Stanner上访者本可以明确写出XV的P
mr. Stanner petitioner could have written explicitly this P of X V given X
written explicitly this P of X V given X of its parts comma theta V but for a
它的零件以逗号V表示，但对于不连续的分销部门，
of its parts comma theta V but for a discrete distribution departments are
discrete distribution departments are really the values of a conditional
实际上，条件分布的值给定了不同的值
really the values of a conditional distribution given different values for
distribution given different values for the node V any tolerance all right so
节点V的任何公差都可以，所以这基本上来自分解
the node V any tolerance all right so this is basically from the factorization
this is basically from the factorization of the directed
指导捆绑的，所以好的，有产品
of the directed a bundle so okay there is the product
a bundle so okay there is the product becomes a summation the launch goes
成为一个总结，发射进入了内部，我一直在磨擦，所以
becomes a summation the launch goes inside and I have been a frictional so
inside and I have been a frictional so let's see I take this donation and VA
让我们看看我接受了这笔捐款，VA则将其捐赠给我，我付了我的总和
let's see I take this donation and VA put it outside I pay I take a summation
put it outside I pay I take a summation over all the immunization for the notes
在所有的免疫接种中，我将其拆分为
over all the immunization for the notes and I split it in estimation over the
and I split it in estimation over the realizations of the family and the
家庭的实现和所有笔记的组织-
realizations of the family and the organization of all the notes - the
organization of all the notes - the problem
问题是我可以这样做吗？
problem am I allowed to do it I split this right
am I allowed to do it I split this right this is estimation over all
这是对所有住院记录的估算，我
this is estimation over all hospitalizations for the notes and I
hospitalizations for the notes and I split it over the family of node V and
将其拆分为节点V的族以及您所知道的除族之外的所有族
split it over the family of node V and everything you know except the family of
everything you know except the family of notes V and all right look now at the
注意V，现在看看内部求和是什么
notes V and all right look now at the inside summation what is the summation
inside summation what is the summation of this on the total count of XV we
在我们介绍的XV总数中，这是我们的
of this on the total count of XV we introduced and definition it was our
introduced and definition it was our second definition of towns so if I take
城镇的第二个定义，所以如果我在这里进行总结
second definition of towns so if I take this summation here what is it
this summation here what is it if I take F of M that's me and I found
如果我取M的F就是我，我发现除了V一家之外的所有东西，他们
if I take F of M that's me and I found everything but the family of V what they
everything but the family of V what they get the personal contact the notes and
得到个人联系的笔记和V的和谐，所以现在我可以
get the personal contact the notes and the harmony of V alright so now I can
the harmony of V alright so now I can you see why immediately the problem the
您会明白为什么MLE会立即估算出这对夫妇的问题，以及为什么您
you see why immediately the problem the MLE estimate the couple's and why you
MLE estimate the couple's and why you can compute the parameters affiliated
可以计算与条件概率不为V相关的参数
can compute the parameters affiliated with the condition probability of not V
with the condition probability of not V independently of other parameters can
独立于其他参数，您可以在这里看到此分解吗
independently of other parameters can you see this decomposition here right
you see this decomposition here right okay separates this right this is for
好吧，分开这个权利，这是针对每个节点V和针对每个节点VI
okay separates this right this is for each node V and for each node V I have
each node V and for each node V I have this summation over all possible
对清漆效果的所有可能实现的总结
this summation over all possible realizations of the varnish effects in
realizations of the varnish effects in the family of being
如此基本的家庭，您可以立即看到
the family of being so basically you can immediately see
so basically you can immediately see that this parameterization only comes
该参数化对于每个节点V仅出现一次，问题是
that this parameterization only comes once for each node V the problem is
once for each node V the problem is convened a couple so we want to complete
召集了一对夫妇，所以我们想完成此参数，所以很明显，我们要
convened a couple so we want to complete this parameter so obviously we're going
this parameter so obviously we're going to maximize this but to maximize it we
为了最大程度地做到这一点，但要最大化它，我们所有人都应该有，所以孩子们我们应该脱钩
to maximize this but to maximize it we all should have so children we decouple
all should have so children we decouple it right we're gonna maximize this with
是的，我们将与他们分别最大化，因为这
it right we're gonna maximize this with them separately okay because this
them separately okay because this parameters appear only in this term but
参数仅在此术语中出现，但我们需要小心，因为
parameters appear only in this term but we need to be careful because since this
we need to be careful because since this is for habilities conditional
是针对能力的条件概率，当您在XV中唱歌时，您拥有
is for habilities conditional probability when you sang in XV you have
probability when you sang in XV you have to get equal to one when you have the
当你有XV的能力给定它的概率时，等于1
to get equal to one when you have the probability of X V given its powers and
probability of X V given its powers and you sominex three it better stands to up
你sominex三个最好站起来好吧，所以基本上你必须放一个
you sominex three it better stands to up okay so basically you have to put a
okay so basically you have to put a Lagrange multiplier and you want to
拉格朗日乘数，您想计算
Lagrange multiplier and you want to compute the Emily estimates for the
compute the Emily estimates for the parameters that define this conditional
定义此条件分布的参数，您必须最大化
parameters that define this conditional distribution you have to maximize that
distribution you have to maximize that and the answer is immediate and an int
答案是即时的，一个int实际上总是说Emily
and the answer is immediate and an int actually always it says that the Emily
actually always it says that the Emily estimate of theta subscript V and
估计下标V，请记住，这确实是有条件的
estimate of theta subscript V and remember really this is the conditional
remember really this is the conditional distribution of X V given its parents to
XV的分配给了它的父母为XP设置了一些值，因此
distribution of X V given its parents to put some values for X P so values for
put some values for X P so values for the parents
我们在这里找的父母是
the parents that's what we're looking here is the
that's what we're looking here is the partial count effects in the commonly
通常将部分计数效应除以X的部分计数就可以了
partial count effects in the commonly divided by the partial count okay of X
对V的说法很有趣，但这很有意义，因此基本上
was fun to the parlance of V but that makes sense so basically the calculated
makes sense so basically the calculated safety of analytics one clinician let a
分析的安全性一名临床医生让极端情况出现，这是错误的，您
safety of analytics one clinician let a extreme condition and it's wrong and you
extreme condition and it's wrong and you won't obey the parameters of that so
将不会遵守该参数，所以您在这里拥有的是
won't obey the parameters of that so what you have here is you have an
what you have here is you have an electronic school and surpass muscles
电子学校，超越您在价值观中观察到的肌肉
electronic school and surpass muscles that the values have observed in your
that the values have observed in your data set for x1 and x2 divided by the
x1和x2的数据集除以您在或中具有的观测值
data set for x1 and x2 divided by the observations that you have or in the
observations that you have or in the particular case if x1 is the comment
如果x1是基本上针对x1的计数的注释的特殊情况是
particular case if x1 is the comment basically for the counts of x1 is that
basically for the counts of x1 is that sort of an expected answer right
某种期望的回答权
我的意思是，这是显而易见的答案，通常，如果您不明白这一点，
basically for the counts of x1 is that sort of an expected answer right
I mean this is the obvious answer and usually if you don't get the obvious
我的意思是，这是显而易见的答案，通常，如果您不明白这一点，
usually if you don't get the obvious answer you're doing something wrong
回答您又在做错事了，这是针对离散分布的
answer you're doing something wrong again this is for discrete distributions
again this is for discrete distributions okay and this is what you get so the
好的，这就是您得到的，所以最重要的是
okay and this is what you get so the bottom line is this
bottom line is this Emily estimate for direct graphical
艾米莉（Emily）对直接图形模型进行估算，夫妻俩还可以，您可以
Emily estimate for direct graphical models the couples okay and you can
models the couples okay and you can solve this problems basically for each
基本上分别为每个节点和这些部分计数解决此问题
solve this problems basically for each node separately and these partial counts
node separately and these partial counts that you get is the sufficient
您获得的是您需要的足够的统计信息，其中包含所有
that you get is the sufficient statistics that you need and contain all
statistics that you need and contain all the information relevant to this local
有关此局部估计和Emily估计问题的信息
the information relevant to this local estimation and Emily estimation problem
estimation and Emily estimation problem for long B so all this estimates are
对于长B，因此所有这些估计对于每个节点都是独立的，所以这
for long B so all this estimates are independent for each node so this
independent for each node so this paradox now I know a definition in the
矛盾的是，我现在知道影片中的班级定义，所以我们要说
paradox now I know a definition in the class in in in the film so we will say
class in in in the film so we will say you know if you try to do this great
您知道现在是否尝试建立出色的模型和概率
you know if you try to do this great models and this probabilities right now
models and this probabilities right now very high-dimensional so you basically
非常高的尺寸，所以您基本上可以将桌子的非常高的尺寸
very high-dimensional so you basically the very high dimension of table to
the very high dimension of table to describe this obviously that is not
形容这显然不是很实际
describe this obviously that is not going to be very practical
going to be very practical I mean if X we can take PI values this
我的意思是，如果X我们可以取PI值，那么可以取20个值，您知道自己迷路了
I mean if X we can take PI values this can take 20 values you know you got lost
can take 20 values you know you got lost okay so what you usually do is you
好吧，所以您通常要做的是用广义来近似
okay so what you usually do is you approximate this with a generalized
approximate this with a generalized linear model so you could basically if
线性模型，因此，如果您将此分布与较少的链接，则基本上可以
linear model so you could basically if you link this distribution with fewer
you link this distribution with fewer parameters in a generalized linear model
广义线性模型中的参数，因此我们已经展示了它们，您可以
parameters in a generalized linear model and so in we have shown them you can go
and so in we have shown them you can go and visit one of the lectures from the
并参观了秋季学期的一堂课，我认为玛丽的书有
and visit one of the lectures from the fall semester I think Mary's book has
fall semester I think Mary's book has this as well as an example you can show
这以及您可以显示的示例，在这种情况下，此归纳和
this as well as an example you can show so in this case this generalizing and
so in this case this generalizing and what is corresponding to each node we
与我们解耦的每个节点对应的是什么
what is corresponding to each node we are decoupled
are decoupled so you can complete the parameters of
因此您可以分别为每个模型分别完成每个模型的参数
so you can complete the parameters of each of these models separately for each
each of these models separately for each node
节点，您在以下方面没有很好的解决方案
node and you didn't have a nice solution in
and you didn't have a nice solution in terms of counts the way that you see
术语计算着您在这里看到的方式，因此您必须解决任何疗法
terms of counts the way that you see here so you have to solve any therapy
here so you have to solve any therapy the way to discuss problem okay
讨论问题的方式好了，所以基本上您能得到的是什么，在哪里
the way to discuss problem okay so basically what you get is and where
so basically what you get is and where he describes problem that you solve
他描述了您迭代解决的问题，但是您可以执行此操作
he describes problem that you solve iteratively but you can do this
iteratively but you can do this algorithm in parallel for its note so in
算法是并行的，因此从本质上讲，您仍然知道总数
algorithm in parallel for its note so in in essence you know the total still
in essence you know the total still becomes even if you have a network of
即使您为此拥有一个表达游戏的网络，它也会变成
becomes even if you have a network of the game of expression for this
the game of expression for this conditional distribution okay so the
有条件的分布还可以，所以我唯一要你不要忘记的地方
conditional distribution okay so the only thing I want you to not forget here
only thing I want you to not forget here is right but it says for completely
是正确的，但它表示对于完全观察到的数据集可以，所以您有
is right but it says for completely observed data sets all right so you have
observed data sets all right so you have begun everything is prescribed in the
开始了起草者规定的一切我什至不是身体，你能吗
begun everything is prescribed in the drafter I'm not even body can you just
drafter I'm not even body can you just if you have hidden variables since I
如果自从我开始以来你有隐藏的变量，我会在最后说些什么
if you have hidden variables since I start I said something intellectual last
start I said something intellectual last time and we're going to come back on it
时间，下周我们将重新讨论，但如果您已隐藏
time and we're going to come back on it next week but if you have hidden
next week but if you have hidden variables how do you you know do you
变量你怎么知道，你有任何机会算法
variables how do you you know do you have any algorithms of chance that you
have any algorithms of chance that you think the same idea can be applied
认为可以应用相同的想法，所以基本上可以以某种方式做一些
think the same idea can be applied so basically somehow you can do some
so basically somehow you can do some iterations and apply some of the same
迭代并应用一些相同的算法，这将允许
iterations and apply some of the same algorithms which will be that will allow
algorithms which will be that will allow you to work with hidden variables and
您使用隐藏变量并观察所有
you to work with hidden variables and observe all
但这是一个价值，所以当您拥有隐藏的力量时，您将如何过活一个人
but this is a value so how will you do a man live when you have hidden powers
man live when you have hidden powers which how do you do Emily when you have
当您有孩子的环境时，您该怎么做Emily
which how do you do Emily when you have kid environments
你怎么做艾米莉·他对粒子有什么只有一种算法
how do you do Emily what he have to the particles there's only one algorithm you
particles there's only one algorithm you know and the guy who you know will be
知道，并且您认识的人会很高兴您不会所有那些外向的人
know and the guy who you know will be happy that you don't all those outward
happy that you don't all those outward p.m. expectation maximization you don't
pm期望最大化您不记得期望最大化否否
p.m. expectation maximization you don't remember expectation maximization no no
remember expectation maximization no no all right you know what is what it isn't
好吧，你知道那是什么，你不知道，然后继续前进
all right you know what is what it isn't you know and you move on okay
期望最大化就可以了，所以您会期望很多
expectation maximization all right so you do expectation much choices all
you do expectation much choices all right okay so we're gonna move back to
好的，所以我们将回到我们正在讨论的问题上
right okay so we're gonna move back to the problem we were discussing on
星期四，尝试看看我们实际上可以做的MLE比指导的更多
Thursday and try to see how we're actually can do MLE more than directed
actually can do MLE more than directed graphical models we will say the problem
图形模型，我们会说问题不会分解好，这是一个
graphical models we will say the problem does not decompose okay and it is a
does not decompose okay and it is a little bit vertically bit complicated
一点点垂直有点复杂，主要是因为这种归一化
little bit vertically bit complicated mainly because of this normalization
mainly because of this normalization factor see the capitana parameters in
因数，请参见图表中的capitana参数，这样
factor see the capitana parameters in the graph okay so
再次保费，并感谢参议员凯恩，我们有左撇子的我们
again premiums and thank the senator Kaine we have any lefty custer's we
Kaine we have any lefty custer's we started before but somehow we would like
之前开始，但不知何故我们想摆脱这些复制品和工作
started before but somehow we would like to get rid of these replicas and work
to get rid of these replicas and work with the probability of one undirected
以一个无方向性的概率大于，因此我们将需要借用一些
with the probability of one undirected more than so we will need to borrow some
more than so we will need to borrow some of the notation reviews from directed
来自有向图的注释评论，这就是为什么我插入那些
of the notation reviews from directed graphs that's why I inserted those
graphs that's why I inserted those slides but this is the main difficult
幻灯片，但这是我们需要别人解决的主要难题
slides but this is the main difficult problem we need others
problem we need others ok so to learn if you give me the
好的，所以要了解一下，如果您给我了解变量中所有变量的实现，
ok so to learn if you give me the realizations of all the variables in the
realizations of all the variables in the graph right this is basically one of the
右图，这基本上是归一化到该乘积的乘积
graph right this is basically one of the normalization till the product of this
normalization till the product of this potential is defined over clicked and
潜力是通过单击确定的，对于今天的讨论，我实际上是
potential is defined over clicked and for the discussion today actually I'm
for the discussion today actually I'm not assuming anything about this click
对此点击不做任何假设，因此您可以使用所需的任何内容，以便他们
not assuming anything about this click so you can use whatever you want so they
so you can use whatever you want so they don't even have to be maximal okay so
甚至不必完全没有问题，因此这些都是点击带来的潜力，而不是
don't even have to be maximal okay so these are potentials over clicks not
these are potentials over clicks not necessarily the normalization factor is
归一化因子基本上是分子，当您
necessarily the normalization factor is basically the numerator here when you
basically the numerator here when you sum over all possible configurations of
极限和放大倍数的所有可能配置的总和是相同的
sum over all possible configurations of extreme and magnification is identical
extreme and magnification is identical to what I used before sure let's go
到我之前使用的内容，确定我们再去一次好吧，请再问一次
to what I used before sure let's go again all right please ask again it
again all right please ask again it doesn't make any sense the probability
没有任何意义的观察概率是
doesn't make any sense the probability for the observations is the product of
for the observations is the product of the likelihood police really described
警察真正描述的阻止右逗号退出的可能性是
the likelihood police really described block right exiting a comma n is the
block right exiting a comma n is the data for the analeptic of the graph
该图的止痛药的数据，其中我给出了所有正确的实现
data for the analeptic of the graph where I given all the realizations right
where I given all the realizations right okay and I write each of this as the
好的，我将所有这些配置都写成产品
okay and I write each of this as the product over all possible configurations
product over all possible configurations to find out now where is the generic
找出通用图G在哪里，我用那个的可能性
to find out now where is the generic graph G and I use the likelihood of that
graph G and I use the likelihood of that for some realizations explained and then
对于一些实现的解释，然后获得副本，我可以事件
for some realizations explained and then to get the replica and I could event a
to get the replica and I could event a function of the exponent right so when X
指数函数的功能，所以当X空缺的另一端结束时，我就在做生意
function of the exponent right so when X vacant side next the end I'm in business
vacant side next the end I'm in business right but by doing this effectively I
是的，但是通过有效地执行此操作，我将不再需要处理此操作
right but by doing this effectively I don't have any more to deal with this
don't have any more to deal with this text become iron okay I'm going to deal
文字变成铁了，好吧，我要处理一个概率模型，哦，天哪
text become iron okay I'm going to deal with one probability model oh my god
with one probability model oh my god I mean why having an erect because this
我的意思是为什么要勃起，因为这就是我想要的工作
I mean why having an erect because this is it this is what I want to work with
is it this is what I want to work with okay no twist there's no rule right I
好吧，没有曲折，没有规则吧，我是说他们是一样的，但是这很多
okay no twist there's no rule right I mean they are the same but this is much
mean they are the same but this is much more elegant so the log of this is so
更加优雅，所以它的日志是，所以我将在这里取日志
more elegant so the log of this is so I'm going to take logs here summation in
I'm going to take logs here summation in N and then I have X V so summation on
N，然后我有XV，所以小VI的所有配置的总和
N and then I have X V so summation on all configurations of little V I have
all configurations of little V I have people and exponents of the Delta
三角函数的人和指数会一次又一次地出现
people and exponents of the Delta function will come in there and again
function will come in there and again what is this this is my count of XV in
这是什么，这是我在数据步骤中对XV的计数
what is this this is my count of XV in my data step alright this is after now
my data step alright this is after now it's identical with before nothing else
它与其他事物完全相同，因此分享就是与众不同，我认为
it's identical with before nothing else so share is the difference and I think
so share is the difference and I think this is what we work for the finish and
这就是我们要完成的工作，而且可爱的符号略有不同
this is what we work for the finish and cutely with slightly different notation
cutely with slightly different notation so now what we do is we'll plug in this
所以现在我们要做的是从我的无向图中插入这个优化
so now what we do is we'll plug in this optimization from my undirected graph so
optimization from my undirected graph so this is number one over Z over the
这是我潜在图的点击次数超过Z的第一名
this is number one over Z over the clicks on my graph of the potential side
clicks on my graph of the potential side C and immediately you appreciate the
C并立即意识到问题，是的，求和
C and immediately you appreciate the problem yes you get the summation over
problem yes you get the summation over the logs of the potentials but also you
势的对数，但是你也得到Z的对数，这是主要的
the logs of the potentials but also you get the log of Z and that's the main
get the log of Z and that's the main should make in all of the rest of
现在应该可以在所有其他图形水域中使用了
should make in all of the rest of graphical waters ok now you get to
graphical waters ok now you get to mission of mmm effectively and you
有效地完成mmm的任务，您还记得这个数量等于
mission of mmm effectively and you remember what is this quantity equal to
remember what is this quantity equal to this book summation what is it if
这本书的总结很糟糕，如果您将所有
this book summation what is it if you take the accounts of all the
you take the accounts of all the variables the limitations of all the
变量所有节点的限制，然后对所有可能的x求和
variables the limitations of all the nodes and you sum for all possible x
nodes and you sum for all possible x rays what do you get
发出光芒，你得到什么，好吧，这就是你得到的
rays what do you get and all right so this is what you get
and all right so this is what you get okay you get summation n XV summation
好吧，您得到的总和为XV的总和，这就是所有这些的集合
okay you get summation n XV summation over maybe a this is the set of all that
over maybe a this is the set of all that makes or maybe I should put here
使或也许我应该把估计放在这里
makes or maybe I should put here estimation over say
estimation over say slide 16 so we hit the correct part and
幻灯片16，所以我们击中了正确的部分，所以现在是这样，然后您就知道了我的光盘
slide 16 so we hit the correct part and so this is and then you know what I disc
so this is and then you know what I disc I am using magic and I write equation on
我正在使用魔术，我也在问题的顶部写了方程式，我想要
I am using magic and I write equation on the top in the question too and I want
the top in the question too and I want you to tell me how a question to came
你告诉我问题是怎么来的，你说亲爱的这么偏
you to tell me how a question to came there are you saying dear so partial
there are you saying dear so partial cows but you have to tell me half of
牛，但你必须告诉我一半，你去了，我做了什么
cows but you have to tell me half of that you went to that what have I done
显然，我没有从点击开始那里教过这种总结
obviously I haven't taught this summation over the click starts there
summation over the click starts there what if I dunno next week but summation
如果我下周不知道但总结我，该怎么办
what if I dunno next week but summation Alex me
我有什么下载servation XP我
what have I download the servation XP I
表示我获得了MXC担保，所以他们花在总和X上是一次多遍估算
mean I secured MXC so they spend on summation X be a multipass estimation
summation X be a multipass estimation illiteracy and another summation of X B
文盲和XB减去C的另一个总和，当我总和时，
illiteracy and another summation of X B minus C and when I sum everything but
minus C and when I sum everything but okay this total content become the
好吧，这些总内容成为XE的部分内容
okay this total content become the partial counts of XE
所以基本上你为什么会知道这一点，因为我只想要这个窍门
so basically why you might know this because I only want this trick to
because I only want this trick to isometric see alright so you can sit
等轴测图可以，如果您对
isometric see alright so you can sit here if you have estimation over the
here if you have estimation over the click okay information over the
在此点击的实现量上可以知道的信息
click okay information over the realizations of the volume of this click
realizations of the volume of this click here is the partial count of XE lava
这是XE熔岩先生的精确计数。 HC的功能
here is the partial count of XE lava precisely mr. function of HC so
precisely mr. function of HC so immediately you can appreciate that the
立即您就会意识到，它们至少是一些分解的
immediately you can appreciate that the least some decomposition they are
least some decomposition they are similar to what we have for the record
类似于我们上次记录的内容，但是Z包含所有参数
similar to what we have for the record last but Z involves all the parameters
last but Z involves all the parameters in the model so we're rolling so that's
在模型中，所以我们进行滚动，这基本上是主要的并发症，
in the model so we're rolling so that's the main complication basically and it
the main complication basically and it is the problem very fundamental not just
这个问题不仅对机器学习非常重要，
is the problem very fundamental not just for machine learning but very
for machine learning but very fundamental in statistical mechanics and
统计力学和其他领域的基本知识可以，所以此列表
fundamental in statistical mechanics and other areas okay all right so this list
other areas okay all right so this list what do we do all right
我们该怎么办
因此，我们需要开始制作一些广告，以了解会发生什么
other areas okay all right so this list what do we do all right
so we need to start doing some ads about to see what is going to come out of this
因此，我们需要开始制作一些广告，以了解会发生什么
to see what is going to come out of this right and I am going to try to optimize
是的，我将尝试就其看到的潜力进行优化
right and I am going to try to optimize with respect to its potentials I see
with respect to its potentials I see okay for its to exchange so here the
可以交换，所以这里的想法是为了保证
okay for its to exchange so here the idea is working for a guarantee
正确，Twix的配置是
right and the configuration of Twix is
给定好，以便我们可以最大化存在齐选择的可能，所以我们
given okay so that we can maximize there is the potential choice Qi okay so we
is the potential choice Qi okay so we take belabor this with respect to C and
相对于C采取这种做法，您马上就可以知道我们这是
take belabor this with respect to C and immediately you can you know we this is
immediately you can you know we this is similar with the record graphs this
与分解的记录图相似，因此我们将拥有
similar with the record graphs this decomposes so we're going to have the
decomposes so we're going to have the passer counts of exceed one / - I see
行人人数超过一/-当您看到这对时，我记得
passer counts of exceed one / - I see remember when you look at this pair
remember when you look at this pair right the precisely concerning what
对，他们正在写的正是与沃尔特有关的东西，好吗
right the precisely concerning what they're writing comes on in Walter okay
they're writing comes on in Walter okay [Applause]
[鼓掌]所以这里的X采取是说采取
[Applause] so this X take here is speaks to take
so this X take here is speaks to take and support fixed realization of the
并支持该问题的固定实现将是成功的，我们只有我的
and support fixed realization of the matter will succeed we only have my
matter will succeed we only have my third choice G of X G and we take
XG的第三选择G，我们对此取微分，所以M
third choice G of X G and we take derivatives with respect to that so M
derivatives with respect to that so M over 1 over C minus 10 times the
超过C的1减去对数导数的10倍，现在我们开始
over 1 over C minus 10 times the derivative of the log and now we start
derivative of the log and now we start getting today's because log of Z the
得到今天的原因是因为拨链器Z的对数将是d的1倍
getting today's because log of Z the derailleur would be 1 over is d times
derailleur would be 1 over is d times the derivative with respect to price G
写入关于X 3和Z的价格G的导数
the derivative with respect to price G of X 3 and Z is written
of X 3 and Z is written remember the Z is the normalization so
记住Z是归一化，所以它的写法是这样
remember the Z is the normalization so it's written like that the potentials
it's written like that the potentials and then I stand all the variables and
然后我忍受了所有变量，因为我不想混淆
and then I stand all the variables and because I don't want to confuse
because I don't want to confuse since I work with a given X P in Cyprus
因为我在塞浦路斯使用给定XP进行工作，所以他们在外部提出了定义
since I work with a given X P in Cyprus the definition they put and externally
the definition they put and externally right because I some every for the
对，因为我每个人都可以进入，好吧，所以让我们
right because I some every for the access get out okay alright so let's
access get out okay alright so let's this is the equation that we started
这是我们开始的等式，所以阿联酋航空现在我已经完成了
this is the equation that we started with so Emirates I see now I have done a
with so Emirates I see now I have done a little bit today right so can be
今天一点点，所以可以欣赏一下瑞克所做的一切
little bit today right so can be appreciate what Rick has been done on
appreciate what Rick has been done on the second line I will need to move that
第二行，我需要将DX的总和移到
the second line I will need to move that summation which are DX outside just to
summation which are DX outside just to simplify my antibodies with so what's
简化我的抗体，因此移动此求和的技巧是什么
simplify my antibodies with so what's the trick here to move this summation of
the trick here to move this summation of curly out I need to be sure that on this
我需要确保在这个学期稍等一下
curly out I need to be sure that on this term wait a second what happened yes
term wait a second what happened yes alright so I need to be sure you can
好吧，所以我需要确保您可以使用
alright so I need to be sure you can vary care of its derivatives with
vary care of its derivatives with respect to precisely for a given X C so
精确地针对给定的XC，因此我需要将其心理功能
respect to precisely for a given X C so I need to put a mental function they
I need to put a mental function they have to be sure that I don't agree in
必须确保我不同意修复中的记忆，我在这里
have to be sure that I don't agree in fix remember in psyche Here I am
我从来没有分享过有关该功能的其他信息
scarily different information outside I've never shared about the function
I've never shared about the function here to be sure that share a morning
这里要确保一个上午的价格相对于T的价格有所不同
here to be sure that share a morning differentiate with respect to price T of
differentiate with respect to price T of X G okay
XG好的，所以这是第三减N 1
X G okay right so this comes third minus N 1 over
right so this comes third minus N 1 over Z there's the function and now in stage
Z有功能，现在在舞台上我有参数或关系
Z there's the function and now in stage here I have the para or for the ties on
here I have the para or for the ties on every click alright and you notice here
每次点击都不错，您会注意到这里已经变成C的xfinity了，
every click alright and you notice here this now became xfinity of C okay and
this now became xfinity of C okay and these are security
这些是安全性，所以您还记得我是否有该文件夹
these are security so you remember if I have the folder
so you remember if I have the folder condition I think they know about this
条件，我认为他们知道关于我在哪里的恐怖
condition I think they know about this with respect to on terror where I'm
with respect to on terror where I'm going to get these proposed that for
将获得这些建议，针对潜在的潜力，除了潜在的街道
going to get these proposed that for focus potentials except potential Street
对，这是您贬值的一种假设，而您却贬值了
right that's an assumption of you depreciate one disappears and you get
depreciate one disappears and you get the product of everything but see in
一切的产物，但现在显然可以看到我该怎么办
the product of everything but see in obviously now what I'm gonna this I'm
obviously now what I'm gonna this I'm gonna multiply resistor and divide by
要乘以电阻并除以误差
gonna multiply resistor and divide by got error
got error so what way inside this chair I am gonna
所以我要在这把椅子上放什么方式再分配X的食物
so what way inside this chair I am gonna get again my food distribution for X
get again my food distribution for X scale this is the rainbabies here I
规模，这是这里的雨婴儿，我会乘以两倍的树
scale this is the rainbabies here I would multiplied with twice tree of
would multiplied with twice tree of carry XP and divide by that so they
携带XP并除以该值，因此它们的乘积项与
carry XP and divide by that so they terms of the multiplied together with
terms of the multiplied together with this will give me back all right so and
这样可以使我恢复正常状态，并且由于我已经完成了此操作，所以现在
this will give me back all right so and now since I have done my accessible this
now since I have done my accessible this little trick I can push the summation
小技巧，我可以将求和的内容推入X技巧的插件中，好吧，
little trick I can push the summation inside plug in X trick here alright and
inside plug in X trick here alright and then what I get this I get from here and
然后我从这里得到的东西，我们将得到的效果告诉我正确的
then what I get this I get from here and we'll get the effects tell me right
we'll get the effects tell me right there is a function inside and I want
里面有一个函数，我想让你告诉我这个总结
there is a function inside and I want you to tell me this summation what will
you to tell me this summation what will it give me so here this is all the
它给了我，所以这就是图表中所有的变量，你说
it give me so here this is all the variables in the graph right and you say
variables in the graph right and you say it's time for possible configurations
是时候进行可能的配置了，但这从任务中向您展示了
it's time for possible configurations but this show you from the very mission
but this show you from the very mission makes a systematic see because X is
进行系统地查看，因为X是固定的，所以我们从中得到了什么
makes a systematic see because X is fixed so what did we get out of it
fixed so what did we get out of it we'll give it here off me okay chin what
我们把它给我，好吧下巴pfx用词作弊是什么
we'll give it here off me okay chin what is pfx cheating with words
人们会看到什么，这是什么意思？
what does people could see with what's what is the name I mean here this
what is the name I mean here this has big tables right position in service
在地面上有大桌子正确的位置
has big tables right position in service in the ground
in the ground now I integrate all the Bible acceptance
现在，我将所有对圣经的接受整合到了固定的点击链上
now I integrate all the Bible acceptance on the clicks chain that I fixed them of
on the clicks chain that I fixed them of the injection XT so that this P of X C
注入XT使得XC的这个P是对应于
the injection XT so that this P of X C is the marginal corresponding to the
is the marginal corresponding to the logistic state of the lights and click
指示灯的逻辑状态，然后单击以查看该状态非常好
logistic state of the lights and click see that's very nice
see that's very nice all right so this gives me the final
好的，这样我得到的最终结果如下
all right so this gives me the final result that looks as follows the
result that looks as follows the derivative of the log likelihood of all
我所有观测值的对数似然的导数是
derivative of the log likelihood of all my observations is the partial count in
my observations is the partial count in my data set of XT divided by this now
我的XT数据集除以现在优化的权利就需要弄清楚
my data set of XT divided by this now optimized right need figure out what
optimized right need figure out what what would lead us the potential and
是什么将带给我们无限的潜力，然后点击查看XT已完成
what would lead us the potential and click see completed of XT right after
click see completed of XT right after night XT is fixed minus n times 1 over
夜间XT固定为XT的PI C的负n乘以1，这是边际
night XT is fixed minus n times 1 over PI C of X T and this is the marginal
PI C of X T and this is the marginal over the click complete aquatics tree
点击完整的水生树，其中一些来自童年
over the click complete aquatics tree some of this comes from childhood comes
some of this comes from childhood comes out and what I get is the this is this
出来，我得到的是，这是嵌套的，它仍然是MLE所重视的
out and what I get is the this is this is nested it is valued at still the MLE
is nested it is valued at still the MLE estimate so the an early estimate toward
估算，以便对边际点击形状计算机的早期估算
estimate so the an early estimate toward the marginal over click shape computer
the marginal over click shape computer visualization extry is NH 3 divided by n
可视化试探是NH 3除以n得出的惊人的无，XJ的M是多少
visualization extry is NH 3 divided by n an amazing without and what is M of XJ
an amazing without and what is M of XJ divided by n what what is on the right
除以n右边的含义是什么，什么名字会给你
divided by n what what is on the right hand side what what name will give you
hand side what what name will give you this this is the partial parent
这是部分母代有效T，所以M效应C除以n
this this is the partial parent effective T so M effects C divided by n
effective T so M effects C divided by n swap what they will you give it is you
交换他们会给你的东西是你不能实现多少次
swap what they will you give it is you can't how many times in realizations you
can't how many times in realizations you have seen the variable sex say capital
看到变性说资本极端采取这些价值观
have seen the variable sex say capital extreme to take these values of
extreme to take these values of next e-service best best M divided by n
下一个电子服务的最佳最佳M除以n，我们应该给它命名
next e-service best best M divided by n which to name we should give to it you
which to name we should give to it you know datasets you have seen this
知道数据集，您已经看到了这种到期时间的组合，那么
know datasets you have seen this combinations of expiry times so what
combinations of expiry times so what does anyone where end
有谁在哪里结束
我们是离散发行，您如何合作
combinations of expiry times so what does anyone where end
we're discrete distributions how do you co-op
拼写它，我可以看到您正在与之抗争，那么战争是什么
spell it I can see you're fighting with it so what's the war
频率好吧，你靠近吧，你知道另一个类似于频率的词
frequency okay you're close right you know another word similar to frequency
并且在字母表中非常接近左1000，而其他在经验之间
and in the alphabet is very close 1000 left and other starts between empirical
left and other starts between empirical distribution right so basically the
分配权，因此基本上最优边际等于
distribution right so basically the optimal marginal is equal to the
optimal marginal is equal to the empirical distribution so basically what
经验分布，所以基本上我们要做的是模态边际
empirical distribution so basically what we have done is the modal marginal
we have done is the modal marginal agrees with in political much the still
如果您认为正确的话，我们在政治上仍然同意令人惊奇的结果
agrees with in political much the still amazing result if you think right we
amazing result if you think right we have done no sanctions anything not even
没有做任何制裁，甚至没有说点击是
have done no sanctions anything not even we haven't even said that the clicks are
we haven't even said that the clicks are much more but the maximal active a
除了功能上的叹息以外，还可以最大程度地发挥作用
much more but the maximal active a destination for this functional sigh
隐含地暗示其在经验模型中的位置的边际为
implicitly implies that the the marginal for its place to the empirical model is
for its place to the empirical model is right objective is to find the potential
正确的目标是找到潜在的另一面信息
right objective is to find the potential side another information is given
side another information is given because
因为
所以他们是偏执的，这与算法无关，这是回归
side another information is given because
so they are devious it doesn't matter this algorithm this this the regression
所以他们是偏执的，这与算法无关，这是回归
this algorithm this this the regression tells you I don't know how they're going
告诉你我不知道他们将如何计算这种潜力，但无论如何
tells you I don't know how they're going to compute this potentials but whatever
to compute this potentials but whatever it is know if you want to pull this
知道是否要拉这个异常估计这个模型的不足
it is know if you want to pull this anomaly estimate this short of the model
anomaly estimate this short of the model marginal can start with the empirical
边际可以从经验盒开始，它不会告诉你那些在哪里
marginal can start with the empirical box it doesn't tell you where those
box it doesn't tell you where those choice would be there is no information
选择将没有该等式的信息，好，为什么没有
choice would be there is no information of this equation okay and why there's no
of this equation okay and why there's no information because unfortunately when
信息，因为不幸的是，当我们采用百万美元的条件时
information because unfortunately when we took the million the steep side terms
we took the million the steep side terms cancel out don't worry this cycle
取消，不要担心此循环，您是否认为其中包含
cancel out don't worry this cycle don't you think is contained inside the
don't you think is contained inside the marginal of pfx shape it's abusive area
pfx形状的边缘是滥用区域
marginal of pfx shape it's abusive area right
right marginal connection also click see and
边际连接也单击“查看”，铅笔实际上是存在的
marginal connection also click see and what is really the pencil existed the
what is really the pencil existed the potential is not a distribution all
潜力不是好的分布，所以这就是您得到的，所以我们将
potential is not a distribution all right so this is what you get so we will
right so this is what you get so we will obviously need to figure out a way to
显然需要找出一种方法来挖掘潜力
obviously need to figure out a way to extract the potentials with some
extract the potentials with some algorithm in a way that satisfies this
算法可以满足此条件，因此我们可以将这些估算称为
algorithm in a way that satisfies this condition so we can call those estimates
condition so we can call those estimates and potentials particles for a very
一组非常特殊的无向图和潜在粒子
and potentials particles for a very particular set of undirected graphs and
particular set of undirected graphs and then we will expect this to be trillion
那么我们将期望这将是我正在使用的简单的万亿有向图
then we will expect this to be trillion directed graphs I'm using a simple
directed graphs I'm using a simple example which were three nodes I am
我正在编写喜剧演员视频的三个节点的示例
example which were three nodes I am writing The Comedians videos one
writing The Comedians videos one potential of electronic spirit another
电子精神的潜力超过X 2 X 3的另一潜力，所以这两个
potential of electronic spirit another potential over X 2 X 3 so this two
potential over X 2 X 3 so this two potentials basically stare down x2 so
势基本上从x2向下凝视，因此显然存在经验
potentials basically stare down x2 so obviously there is an empirical
obviously there is an empirical counterfactual and X you remember the
事实与事实相反，您还记得演讲者需要一件奇迹般的礼服，所以
counterfactual and X you remember the speaker needs a miracle gown so there is
speaker needs a miracle gown so there is an empirical count X 2 and X 3 and you
经验数X 2和X 3，你知道我要给你什么
an empirical count X 2 and X 3 and you know what I am going to give you what
know what I am going to give you what the you know what the summation will
您知道该模型的总和会是什么样子
the you know what the summation will look like for the model for the
look like for the model for the underneath solution okay what's the
在解决方案下面好吧，最初的问题是什么，您可以告诉我是否
underneath solution okay what's the initial issue and you can tell me if I'm
initial issue and you can tell me if I'm right or wrong okay
对还是错好吧，我的意思是没事，所以我要走了
right or wrong okay I mean nothing all right so I am going
I mean nothing all right so I am going to tell you that the MLE estimate okay
告诉您，MLE估算值是由该经验边际x 1给出的
to tell you that the MLE estimate okay is given by this empirical marginal x 1
is given by this empirical marginal x 1 x 2 x this is physical marginal but
x 2 x这是物理边际，但除以极限物理模型
x 2 x this is physical marginal but divided by the physical model of extreme
divided by the physical model of extreme and can you do some checking and tell me
你可以做些检查，告诉我这是满足条件的吗
and can you do some checking and tell me that this is satisfies the condition
that this is satisfies the condition that we had before so really we can call
以前我们曾经有过，所以我们可以称其为艾米丽（Emily）估计
that we had before so really we can call it an Emily estimate
it an Emily estimate I say this is the solution and I want
我说这是解决方案，我要你告诉我该解决方案是
I say this is the solution and I want you to tell me that that solution is
you to tell me that that solution is actually satisfying this so can you tell
真正满足这个要求，所以您能告诉我有关大门的事吗，请记住
actually satisfying this so can you tell me about the gate so remember the
me about the gate so remember the imminent question is not the mountain
迫在眉睫的问题不是南希山必须等于
imminent question is not the mountain Nancy that has to be equal to the
Nancy that has to be equal to the empirical module this is my mother
经验模块这是我妈妈，我假设这是模型
empirical module this is my mother i postulate this is the model take the
i postulate this is the model take the margin I would say of x1 and x2 all
我会说x1和x2的裕度，所以从中取裕度
margin I would say of x1 and x2 all right so take from this the margin of
right so take from this the margin of affection are x2 what do we need to do
情感是x2，我们需要做些什么才能得到非零的反射
affection are x2 what do we need to do to get a nonzero reflection on
to get a nonzero reflection on experience from this approximation here
从这里的近似值中获得经验，但我推测可能是在我的答案中
experience from this approximation here but i postulate that maybe in my answer
but i postulate that maybe in my answer to get the mountain of x1 x2 what do I
要得到x1 x2的山峰，我需要做什么？
to get the mountain of x1 x2 what do I need to do how do you not generalize
声波3，所以当您在x3上唱歌时，您会到达这里的声音会被取消，所以
sonic 3 so when you sang on x3 what will you get here that will cancel out so you
you get here that will cancel out so you get that the modern marginal of x1 x2 is
得到x1 x2的现代边际是Flextronics要做的经验模块
get that the modern marginal of x1 x2 is the empirical module Flextronics to do
the empirical module Flextronics to do the same thing and marginalize the chain
如果您提到不合逻辑的x1，则同样的事情会使x1上的链边缘化
the same thing and marginalize the chain on the on x1 if you mention illogical x1
on the on x1 if you mention illogical x1 this will give you the empirical
这将为您提供X 2的经验边际，将取消该列表
this will give you the empirical marginal of X 2 will cancel out the list
marginal of X 2 will cancel out the list and then you get the empirical version
然后得到X 2和X 3的经验版本，这样就可以满足
and then you get the empirical version of X 2 and X 3 so this satisfies
of X 2 and X 3 so this satisfies actually all the properties there so it
实际上那里的所有属性，所以这是正确的解决方案，所以我怎么得到
actually all the properties there so it is the correct solution so how did I get
is the correct solution so how did I get this relation here is the trick what a
这种关系在这里是诀窍，我认为我之前的业务是什么
this relation here is the trick what a business I think the text of ahead of my
business I think the text of ahead of my problem like X 1 X 2 X 2 X 3
像X 1 X 2 X 2 X 3这样的问题
problem like X 1 X 2 X 2 X 3 I took the empirical couch over this
I took the empirical couch over this place so these are my empirical
放置，所以这些不是我的经验知识，因为分裂
place so these are my empirical knowledge not and because the splits
knowledge not and because the splits have another lost over this now the X 2
X 2 I除以现在的边际
have another lost over this now the X 2 I divided by the marginal of now that
好吧，因此下一波您实际上可以做这类事情的浪潮被称为
okay so the next wave you can actually do this type of things are called the
do this type of things are called the composable drops alright and so she's
好的滴剂很好，所以她说得对，可以的玻璃杯还可以
composable drops alright and so she's right the composable glass right okay
right the composable glass right okay and here's one glass that is not
这是一个不可分解的杯子，您将无法
and here's one glass that is not decomposable for you won't be able to
decomposable for you won't be able to actually do this trick so this idea of
实际上是做这个技巧，所以这个从顶峰边缘开始的想法和
actually do this trick so this idea of starting with the pinnacle marginals and
starting with the pinnacle marginals and trying to guess where the solution will
试图猜测解决方案将不会真正应用于此问题的方法
trying to guess where the solution will not actually apply to this problem okay
not actually apply to this problem okay and and the reason is not because this
而且原因不是因为它看起来不错，这无济于事
and and the reason is not because this has a look all right this is nothing to
has a look all right this is nothing to do out at the end of the day you have a
一天结束时去看看，但是这里有一个事实，那就是
do out at the end of the day you have a look here but here's liver the fact that
look here but here's liver the fact that this what you see here is not a
您在这里看到的不是可分解的下落，那是什么
this what you see here is not a decomposable drop so what's the
decomposable drop so what's the definition of a decomposable graph the
分解图的定义如果可以的话，眼镜就成为可能
definition of a decomposable graph the glasses are become possible if we can
glasses are become possible if we can divide it into this joint into various
把它分成这个关节，分成各种关节单元
divide it into this joint into various joint cells adn s where s the parade a
joint cells adn s where s the parade a and B and s is complete
并且B和s是完整的subsuble知识属是集体的
and B and s is complete chasuble knowledge genus are collective
chasuble knowledge genus are collective okay so if you look on this graph I can
好吧，所以如果你看这张图，我可以将你从这方面的知识中分离出来
okay so if you look on this graph I can divide you from this knowledge of this
divide you from this knowledge of this node and that node and obviously in this
节点和该节点，显然在此S注释中，x2单独存在于
node and that node and obviously in this S note here x2 separate sexual in
S note here x2 separate sexual in extreme right and I can do the same
极端权利，我可以在这里做同样的事情，我可以将其划分为
extreme right and I can do the same thing here I can divide this to be the
thing here I can divide this to be the set a this node x4 to be the certainty
将这个节点x4设置为确定性，并将x2和x3相连
set a this node x4 to be the certainty and x2 and x3 that are connected they
and x2 and x3 that are connected they separate x2 and x4
将x2和x4分开，但是如果移至该图，则可以
separate x2 and x4 but if you move to this graph you can
but if you move to this graph you can try if you try to define how to define a
尝试如果您尝试定义如何定义bns，除非没有成功，否则我们不会成功
try if you try to define how to define a bns we are not going to succeed unless
bns we are not going to succeed unless you actually add extra edges from this
您实际上可以从该图中添加额外的边缘，除非您有额外的
you actually add extra edges from this graph all right unless you had extra
graph all right unless you had extra edges to this graph
图的边缘，让我告诉你，你知道我知道
edges to this graph and let me tell you and you know I know
and let me tell you and you know I know what I'm going to be able to discuss
我将在本课程中讨论的内容
what I'm going to be able to discuss this in this course
this in this course remember when we do will the very early
记得当我们做的时候会在课程的最初阶段做一个图表
remember when we do will the very early part of the course we were doing a graph
part of the course we were doing a graph elimination so nothing that you do graph
消除，因此您无需在此处进行图消除的任何操作，并非如此
elimination so nothing that you do graph elimination here right and it's not
elimination here right and it's not eliminating any note it doesn't matter
消除任何音符并不重要，它们都是对称的，所以如果您发光
eliminating any note it doesn't matter they're all symmetric so if you luminate
they're all symmetric so if you luminate explore what do you need to go to the
探索您需要进行下一步操作的内容，如果需要对此进行分析
explore what do you need to go to the next step if you need to analyze this
next step if you need to analyze this idea the composability for this class it
想到这个类的可组合性，它直接与图形链接
idea the composability for this class it is directly linked with the graph
is directly linked with the graph elimination algorithm all right and to
消除算法，直到最后
elimination algorithm all right and to hell and actually at the end of the day
hell and actually at the end of the day they're directly linked with the
它们与结点3的输出直接链接好，所以如果图形是
they're directly linked with the junction 3 output ok so if the graph is
junction 3 output ok so if the graph is the compulsive vote the solution is
强制性投票解决方案是微不足道的，还有更多
the compulsive vote the solution is trivial all right and there is more
trivial all right and there is more discussion in the launch
在启动中进行讨论好的，所以它说如果图形不是
discussion in the launch ok ok so it says if the graph is not
ok ok so it says if the graph is not become possible basically there's
成为可能，基本上，现在你无能为力
become possible basically there's nothing you can do with the present
nothing you can do with the present curve of the immediate so we need to do
立即数的曲线，所以我们需要做得更好，因为时间是
curve of the immediate so we need to do something better so since the time is
something better so since the time is clicking so let's see what we will do if
单击，让我们看看如果图是遗传算法，我们将如何处理
clicking so let's see what we will do if the algorithm if graph is a genetic
the algorithm if graph is a genetic graph and we cannot use this the
图，我们不能使用这个组成基本上成为可能
graph and we cannot use this the composition become possibility basically
composition become possibility basically of the graph so we're going to develop
的图形，所以我们要进行评估，我们称其为疗法
of the graph so we're going to develop evaluate let's call it therapy
evaluate let's call it therapy proportional thinking part of this
这个喷嘴延续的比例思维部分是关于
proportional thinking part of this nozzle continuation be a lecture on
nozzle continuation be a lecture on Tuesday but we're going to come back so
星期二，但我们要回来了，所以我们可以完成课程，让我们看看
Tuesday but we're going to come back so we can finish the course so let's see
we can finish the course so let's see what is our waitress remember when we
我们的女服务员还记得什么时候我们采用对数似然的梯度
what is our waitress remember when we took the gradient of the log likelihood
took the gradient of the log likelihood we basically regret the use this pair -
我们基本上后悔使用这对-绝望你还记得我们说过
we basically regret the use this pair - despair you remember we said that
despair you remember we said that child-sized cancel out so you know now
儿童尺寸的取消，所以您现在知道我们要去伙计们
child-sized cancel out so you know now we're going guys
we're going guys ok this
确定这个raishin网站的可能性更大
ok this raishin site with more the likelihood
raishin site with more the likelihood implicitly right so then I guess I am
隐含的是正确的，所以我想我不会完全摆脱它，但是
implicitly right so then I guess I am NOT going to get rid of precisely but
NOT going to get rid of precisely but I'm gonna plate and tell at the fixed
我要盘算，并使用以下等式告诉定点算法：
I'm gonna plate and tell at the fixed point algorithm using this equation as
point algorithm using this equation as follows
跟随我就是我要去的基础
follows I am what I'm going to based I am going
I am what I'm going to based I am going to use so this is my empirical marginal
使用，所以这是我的经验边际还是a，我要除以我的
to use so this is my empirical marginal or a is there I am going to divide by my
or a is there I am going to divide by my previous guests as the modern marginal
以前的客人是现代的边缘人，这就是我的异国情调的茶
previous guests as the modern marginal which is this but interracial tea I am
which is this but interracial tea I am going to multiply with my estimate for
将与我对茶和茶的迭代潜力的估计相乘
going to multiply with my estimate for the potential of iteration of tea and
the potential of iteration of tea and then we all the term on the other side
那么即使您更新时间T加1，我们在另一侧的所有项
then we all the term on the other side even when you update the time T plus 1
你应该在这里发生，我把它带到他们推动的右边
you should happen here right I took this to the right hand side they push
to the right hand side they push everything to the left all right
一切都在左边，好吧，所以这东西在右边
everything to the left all right so the this thing on the right hand side
so the this thing on the right hand side would be mighty plus small update based
将是强大的，再加上根据前九个项目的估算进行的小更新
would be mighty plus small update based on the estimate of the previous nine
on the estimate of the previous nine times the ratio of this empirical margin
乘以该经验保证金之比除以先前的估计保证金
times the ratio of this empirical margin divided by the previous estimated margin
divided by the previous estimated margin of clickstream now you know conventional
的点击流，现在您知道常规方法已经在数值分析中做到了这一点
of clickstream now you know conventional have done this in numerical analysis you
have done this in numerical analysis you know it's not like you play trivia
知道这不像您玩琐事问题，然后我们除以一些未知数
know it's not like you play trivia question we divide by some unknown then
question we divide by some unknown then you do a fixed point iteration somehow
您以某种方式进行定点迭代，这东西会转换为假设否
you do a fixed point iteration somehow this thing converts the assumption is no
this thing converts the assumption is no guarantee that this will actually makes
确保这实际上在注释中有任何意义，但我不
guarantee that this will actually makes any sense well in the notes and I don't
any sense well in the notes and I don't know how much time we have there is a
知道我们有多少时间只有一个推进装置
know how much time we have there is a propulsion unit only that this is
propulsion unit only that this is working the naturally maximizes them
自然地工作会最大化他们喜欢的可能性，所以实际上
working the naturally maximizes them they love likelihood so it's actually
they love likelihood so it's actually the more than the standard wave as well
比标准波形还好，所以让我们看看这是怎么回事
the more than the standard wave as well okay and so let's see how this so this
okay and so let's see how this so this is how this thing works
这件事是如何运作的，我不会经历
is how this thing works all right I am NOT gonna go through the
all right I am NOT gonna go through the points because the drop is wanted before
点，因为之前想要滴，但让我告诉你两件事，你
points because the drop is wanted before but let me tell you two things that you
but let me tell you two things that you know they know she's actually
知道他们知道她实际上只有代数有两个
know they know she's actually there's just algebra there are two
there's just algebra there are two things that happen when you iterate with
当您使用此算法进行迭代时，发生的事情需要您
things that happen when you iterate with this algorithm number one demands you
this algorithm number one demands you know at every iteration is equal to the
知道每次迭代都等于经验边际，所以如果这意味着您
know at every iteration is equal to the empirical marginal so if it means as you
empirical marginal so if it means as you implement you subscribe in the liquor
实施您订阅的白酒贸易展览会就像您继续前进并
implement you subscribe in the liquor trade show is like you keep going and
trade show is like you keep going and clapping the prevent you will suffice to
拍手，您将足以说出模型模块等于
clapping the prevent you will suffice to say that the model module is equal to
say that the model module is equal to the empirical much stuff we position you
我们为您定位的经验丰富的东西满足了它们并进行了归一化
the empirical much stuff we position you satisfy them and the normalization
satisfy them and the normalization factor does not change okay and I want
因素不会改变，我想给你，基本上，这是MLE
factor does not change okay and I want to give you so basically this is the MLE
to give you so basically this is the MLE property right of all iterations the
所有迭代的属性权大于边际等于
property right of all iterations the more than marginal is equal to the
more than marginal is equal to the empirical milestone thus it doesn't
经验上的里程碑，因此它没有改变，但我想给你一个
empirical milestone thus it doesn't change but I wanted to give you a
change but I wanted to give you a position of this time with it
这一次的位置，这就是我们得出的结果，您实际上可以
position of this time with it this is what we derive you can actually
this is what we derive you can actually show this very important you can throw
说明这一点非常重要，您可以从该方程式中抛出，可以说明
show this very important you can throw from this equation you can show the
from this equation you can show the algorithm takes the form that you see on
算法采用的形式只是您在一个关于语言的问题上看到的问题，而
algorithm takes the form that you see on just a question on the lingual okay and
just a question on the lingual okay and I'm going to rewrite this equation in a
我将以总欺诈的形式来重写此等式，
I'm going to rewrite this equation in a form of the total fraud you can which
form of the total fraud you can which orientation you can come up with it
方向，无需任何数学就可以提出来，所以我的意思是
orientation you can come up with it without any mathematics okay so I mean
without any mathematics okay so I mean give you proof of this you can show the
给您证明，您可以证明证明实际上是两行，但这
give you proof of this you can show the proof is actually two lines but this
proof is actually two lines but this algorithm you can show that the
算法，您可以证明X恰好位于
algorithm you can show that the probability of X being right on the
probability of X being right on the whole at iteration T plus one is your
迭代T的整体加一是您的估计持续时间T乘以经验值
whole at iteration T plus one is your estimated duration T times the empirical
estimated duration T times the empirical marginal
边缘剪辑状态除以北部
marginal clip state divided by the northern
clip state divided by the northern margin out at Creek stream I mean you
在Creek stream边距，我的意思是您在工作时可以知道
margin out at Creek stream I mean you can you know when you're working this
can you know when you're working this right you will operate on
正确，您将在Trixie上工作，这样您就可以理解为什么我可以
right you will operate on Trixie so you can appreciate why I can
Trixie so you can appreciate why I can stop the disguise here with a whole
在这里以整个概率分布停止伪装，因为
stop the disguise here with a whole probability distribution because
probability distribution because socialism doesn't change so it's not
社会主义不会改变，所以这不像您从P加1转到P
socialism doesn't change so it's not like you go from P plus 1 to P and this
like you go from P plus 1 to P and this is going to ring you because they always
会打扰您，因为他们总是可以让第二站保持正常，所以让我
is going to ring you because they always can keep the second stop okay so let me
can keep the second stop okay so let me I'm going to take this equation and I'm
我将采用这个方程式，然后将其重写
I'm going to take this equation and I'm gonna rewrite it
gonna rewrite it okay so whatever it is I am keeping this
好吧，无论发生什么，我都将其保持在临界边缘，​​我
okay so whatever it is I am keeping this in critical marginal there and I am
in critical marginal there and I am taking this divided by God and I'm going
把这个除以上帝，我将在迭代P中写这个，我是
taking this divided by God and I'm going to write this at iteration P and I'm
to write this at iteration P and I'm going to write it as the conditional of
给定你从未玩过的XT，将其写为XV减去T的条件
going to write it as the conditional of X V minus T given XT you never played
X V minus T given XT you never played that risk / that is the conditional of
该风险/在极端情况下是XT减去T的条件，我的意思是，如果您
that risk / that is the conditional of XT minus T given extreme I mean if you
XT minus T given extreme I mean if you are going to expire right this would be
即将到期，这将是这与不是的结合
are going to expire right this would be the joint of this and that which is not
the joint of this and that which is not divided by the modal marginal extreme
除以模态边际极值，现在什么也没做，为什么我会这样
divided by the modal marginal extreme nothing now why am i doing like this
nothing now why am i doing like this this is how the graph looks like
这就是图表看起来很好，很直觉的地方
this is how the graph looks like all right and very intuition here what
all right and very intuition here what do you do you're actually changing the
您是否真的在改变潜在的冲突，看看您是否知道
do you do you're actually changing the potential conflict see you know of the
potential conflict see you know of the notes on click G so equation tells us
单击G时的注释，所以等式告诉我们您知道进行联合的数学测试
notes on click G so equation tells us you know math test to make the joint
you know math test to make the joint probability distribution of step T plus
步骤T加1的概率分布使用先前的条件
probability distribution of step T plus 1 use the previous conditional where the
1 use the previous conditional where the body missions still are not updated and
车身任务仍未更新，并且第一行数据中的任何内容均不可用
body missions still are not updated and anything in first line of data marginal
anything in first line of data marginal on extreme
在极端
好的，所以您保留先前的内容，请在这里再次退出
anything in first line of data marginal on extreme
all right so you keep the previous again exit here
好的，所以您保留先前的内容，请在这里再次退出
exit here this is the conditional from the
这是先前模型乘以新边际的条件
this is the conditional from the previous model times the new marginal
previous model times the new marginal which is basically it is so yeah
这基本上是这样，是的，基本上XJ上的边际
which is basically it is so yeah basically the marginal on XJ with
basically the marginal on XJ with empirical master very clearly allowed
如果您考虑一下，经验丰富的大师非常清楚地允许救济
empirical master very clearly allowed relief if you think about it and this
relief if you think about it and this algorithm is applicable sort of to any
该算法适用于它没有的任何类型的无向图
algorithm is applicable sort of to any type of undirected graph it doesn't have
type of undirected graph it doesn't have to be you know become possible you know
成为可能的你知道还没说什么
to be you know become possible you know haven't really said anything about that
haven't really said anything about that the police have to be much small so it's
警察必须很小，所以又可以看到尼斯小姐
the police have to be much small so it's and again you can see miss nice the
and again you can see miss nice the details there is a profit rate that this
细节有一个利润率，随着您迭代次数的增加，利润率会增加
details there is a profit rate that this increases as you iterate a much more
increases as you iterate a much more likelihood and in even give you life
可能性，甚至给您提供三个迭代的生命解决方案，
likelihood and in even give you life solution of the three iterations by the
solution of the three iterations by the way if the graph is like impossible I
如果图好像不可能的话，我认为您可以一次迭代地执行此操作
way if the graph is like impossible I think you do this in one iteration
think you do this in one iteration converges to right answer yep
收敛到正确的答案
当人们以前学习但整个事物实际上是直接联系在一起的
think you do this in one iteration converges to right answer yep
when people study before but the whole thing is of directly linked actually
当人们以前学习但整个事物实际上是直接联系在一起的
thing is of directly linked actually yeah exactly
是的，因为算法基本上是正确的
yeah exactly okay as an algorithm is basically the
okay as an algorithm is basically the most general a lot of good is right but
最一般的说，很多好处是对的，但是这两件事是直接联系在一起的
most general a lot of good is right but so the two things are directly linked
so the two things are directly linked here okay so the exact elimination
这里好吧，所以确切的消除算法是一个结点树算法，
here okay so the exact elimination algorithm a junction tree algorithm and
algorithm a junction tree algorithm and what you see here have the same origin
您在这里看到的东西具有相同的起源
是算法，我将以某种方式为您提供一些东西
algorithm a junction tree algorithm and what you see here have the same origin
is algorithm and I'm going to give you something that somehow when I was
是算法，我将以某种方式为您提供一些东西
something that somehow when I was looking at your Mike Jordans knows that
看着你的迈克·乔丹斯（Mike Jordans）知道，我前段时间给了你，她有一个
looking at your Mike Jordans knows that I gave you some time ago she has a
I gave you some time ago she has a derivation of this IPF algorithm that is
这种IPF算法的推导，用不到一个就非常有趣
derivation of this IPF algorithm that is very interesting using short of one
very interesting using short of one identity we have never seen and most
我们从未见过的身份，很可能很少有人会使用
identity we have never seen and most probably very few people use okay and
probably very few people use okay and and something we have discussed at least
我们讨论过的东西，至少我们与我们讨论过的，我们参加了该课程
and something we have discussed at least we discussed with us we took the course
we discussed with us we took the course in the fall
在秋天我们应该给你，你可以得到
in the fall shall we give you that you can derive
shall we give you that you can derive all of these things using a minimization
所有这些都使用适当的KL发散距离的最小化
all of these things using a minimization of an appropriate KL divergence distance
of an appropriate KL divergence distance and that you to minimize is basically
而您要最小化的基本上是给定theta的x的P之间的距离
and that you to minimize is basically the distance between P of x given theta
the distance between P of x given theta and the empirical distribution P of X
X的经验分布P对，您需要做的是
and the empirical distribution P of X right and what you need to do is you can
right and what you need to do is you can show by the way
顺便说一句，让我说你的事情
show by the way so let me say that things that you
so let me say that things that you should know by now if you want to
现在应该知道是否要最大化这种可能性
should know by now if you want to maximize the likelihood this is
maximize the likelihood this is equivalent to minimizing the distance of
等效于将X的P与经验分布的距离最小化
equivalent to minimizing the distance of P of X from the empirical distribution
P of X from the empirical distribution picture via text that's the standard
如果要最大化图像，可以通过文本作为标准理论进行图片处理
picture via text that's the standard theory all right if you want to maximize
theory all right if you want to maximize the likelihood the derivation sphere is
导数范围与最小化范围相同的可能性
the likelihood the derivation sphere is the same as minimize
the same as minimize distance from the empirical distribution
距离经验分布因子的距离，这是凉爽因素之一
distance from the empirical distribution factor that's part one factor the cool
factor that's part one factor the cool but liberal distance D between some
但是某个分布P与另一个分布之间的自由距离D
but liberal distance D between some distribution P from another distribution
distribution P from another distribution Q when I split the variables in two sets
当我将变量分为两组时，可以将Q记为a，将B记为a
Q when I split the variables in two sets a and B can be written down in a in a
a and B can be written down in a in a sort of very nice decomposition that is
第二行给出的一种非常好的分解，因此，如果您
sort of very nice decomposition that is given by the second line here so if you
given by the second line here so if you need the distance between P of X a X B
需要X X XB的P和X X或XB的Q之间的距离，可以写成
need the distance between P of X a X B and Q of X or X B you can write this as
and Q of X or X B you can write this as the difference between the marginals and
边际之间的差异和条件之间的距离
the difference between the marginals and the distance between the conditionals
the distance between the conditionals after it's over let's say all right okay
结束之后，让我们说好吧，所以我要做的是，这不是
after it's over let's say all right okay so what I'm gonna do is so this is not
so what I'm gonna do is so this is not something you see often but it comes
您经常看到的东西，但是它在我们的问题中非常方便，因为如果您
something you see often but it comes very handy in our problem because if you
very handy in our problem because if you use this idea but much maizing the
使用这个想法，但是很多玉米的可能性和我想象的一样
use this idea but much maizing the likelihood is the same as me imagine
likelihood is the same as me imagine this distance and it's life is this
这个距离，它的生命就是这个令人困惑的方程式，您将得到
this distance and it's life is this confusing this equation you're shall get
confusing this equation you're shall get the same answer as what you know
与您所知道的直接做我展示的代数的答案相同
the same answer as what you know directly doing the algebra that I show
directly doing the algebra that I show you before and here is the how the scale
您之前和这里是距离的尺度如何在我们自己的身上表现出来的
you before and here is the how the scale of distance manifests itself in our
of distance manifests itself in our problem so what are those two be noise
问题，那么这两个是什么噪声模型与模型之间的距离
problem so what are those two be noise the distance between the model and the
the distance between the model and the empirical distribution is the same as
经验分布与您所知道的相同，我们必须将距离写为
empirical distribution is the same as you know we have to write as distance as
you know we have to write as distance as the distance between the marginals and
边缘之间的距离，我正在使用HC之间的电位
the distance between the marginals and I'm using the potential to HC between
I'm using the potential to HC between the model and the empirical and then I
模型和经验，然后我得到涉及
the model and the empirical and then I have this average that involves the
have this average that involves the conditionals as given exchange shall be
作为给定交换的条件仅是我想要的等式
conditionals as given exchange shall be only further this equation that I want
only further this equation that I want to minimize with respect to X T is this
相对于XT最小化是这次，这是不安全的
to minimize with respect to X T is this time this is not secure that ship has
time this is not secure that ship has been tomorrow
明天到了
那么您如何最小化此边际和此边之间的距离，以及
time this is not secure that ship has been tomorrow
so how do you minimize the distance between this marginal and this and
那么您如何最小化此边际和此边之间的距离，以及
between this marginal and this and critical Martina obviously this should
关键的玛蒂娜（Martina）显然这应该等于那个，这就是我们
critical Martina obviously this should be equal to that and that's what we
be equal to that and that's what we proved before so there is a proofing on
之前被证明过，所以对生活的检验是正确的，而你又一次不知道
proved before so there is a proofing on life right and again you never know
life right and again you never know where and how things will be useful but
事情在哪里和如何会有用，但这不是吉隆坡的组成
where and how things will be useful but this not is the composition of the KL
this not is the composition of the KL it's actually very handy because it
它实际上非常方便，因为它可以为您提供答案，而无需
it's actually very handy because it gives you an answer no need to the
gives you an answer no need to the gradient and you know you can use ideas
渐变，您知道您可以使用渐变下降的想法，所以我们可以
gradient and you know you can use ideas from a gradient descent so we can please
from a gradient descent so we can please so rather than doing this fixed point
因此，除了执行此定点迭代算法外，您还可以介绍
so rather than doing this fixed point iteration algorithm you can introduce
iteration algorithm you can introduce some learning rate and a real life is a
一些学习率和现实生活中的梯度方程就是梯度，所以你
some learning rate and a real life is a gradient equation is the gradient so you
gradient equation is the gradient so you can put some learning rate law and you
可以制定一些学习率定律，并且您可以继续进行出色的更新
can put some learning rate law and you can keep doing update in a fantastic
can keep doing update in a fantastic regular sense if you apply the solver if
如果您今天讨论的唯一问题是您是否使用求解器，这是常识
regular sense if you apply the solver if the discuss today the only thing is you
the discuss today the only thing is you need to just be careful because the
只需小心一点，因为Z的罗马化成本必须为
need to just be careful because the romanization cost from Z has to be
romanization cost from Z has to be recalculated at each iteration doesn't
如果您每次迭代都重新计算，则不会一次又一次保持不变
recalculated at each iteration doesn't remain constant right and again if you
remain constant right and again if you have latent variables basically what you
具有潜在变量基本上，您需要做的是
have latent variables basically what you need to do is that for the rest of the
need to do is that for the rest of the wacky graphs you can apply exactly the
古怪的图，您可以应用与今天需要讨论的图完全相同的图，但是您
wacky graphs you can apply exactly the same that needs to discuss today but you
same that needs to discuss today but you apply them artistic iteration of the e/m
将它们向外应用e / m的艺术迭代，这样您就可以真正做到这一点
apply them artistic iteration of the e/m outwards so really you can do this for
outwards so really you can do this for any problem with hidden variables very
隐藏变量的任何问题都很简单的方法来估计参数
any problem with hidden variables very simple way to estimate the parameters
simple way to estimate the parameters assuming that you have complete data
假设您有完整的数据描述，如果市民说不，
assuming that you have complete data description all right if civics says no
description all right if civics says no we have noticed they know no lecture on
我们注意到他们不知道星期五没有演讲，好吧，我打算说，如果我们
we have noticed they know no lecture on Friday okay and I'm going to maybe if we
Friday okay and I'm going to maybe if we have a lecture next Friday but there's
下个星期五有个演讲会，但是星期二和星期四没有个演讲会
have a lecture next Friday but there's no lecture on Tuesday and Thursday okay
no lecture on Tuesday and Thursday okay all right
好吧，等等，所以我们下次见
all right so and and and so we'll see you next
so and and and so we'll see you next week
星期